Lat Lat_Joor Lat_Joor PER 0.994295226107 Lat-Dior B-PER
Joor None I-PER

' None O
'' None O
Madrid None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
rééwum None O
Ispaañ Ispaañ Ispaañ GPE 0.999996832097 Spain B-LOC
. None O

Tugal Tugal Tugal GPE 1.0 Europe B-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar_Region B-LOC
Ndakaaru None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu None O
Ndakaaru None O
'' None O
' None O
, None O
benn None O
la None O
ci None O
fukk None O
ak None O
juroom-ñenti None O
diiwaan None O
yu None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
. None O

Poortorikoo Poortorikoo Poortorikoo GPE 0.999999989776 Puerto_Rico B-LOC

Watikaa Watikaa Watikaa GPE 0.999998919962 Vatican_City B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Wu-angalteer None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
làkk None O
wa None O
ñuy None O
wax None O
te None O
juddoo None O
ca None O
Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo GPE 0.999997203683 United_Kingdom B-LOC
yi None O

' None O
'' None O
Kureelu None O
temb None O
bu None O
Poortorikoo None O
'' None O
' None O
bi None O
( None O
ci None O
Ispaañ Ispaañ Ispaañ GPE 0.999996832097 Spain B-LOC
: None O
partido None O
Indipendentista None O
Puertorriqueño None O
) None O
, None O
ab None O
kureelu None O
politigu None O
Poortorikoo Poortorikoo Poortorikoo GPE 0.999999989776 Puerto_Rico B-LOC
la None O
buy None O
yëngu None O
ngir None O
Poortorikoo Poortorikoo Poortorikoo GPE 0.999999989776 Puerto_Rico B-LOC
am None O
tembteem None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu None O
Kawlax None O
'' None O
' None O
benn None O
la None O
ci None O
juroom-ñenti None O
diiwaani None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
. None O

Diiwaanu None O
Tambaakundaa Diiwaanu_Tambaakundaa Tambaakundaa GPE 1.0 Tambacounda_Region B-LOC
ci None O
penku None O
; None O

' None O
'' None O
Uetersen None O
'' None O
' None O
( None O
ˈyːtɐzən None O
) None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Almaañ Almaañ Almaañ GPE 0.999994565441 Germany B-LOC
. None O

Benn None O
la None O
ci None O
fukk None O
ak None O
ñenti None O
diiwaan None O
yu None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Minsk None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Belaarus Belaarus Belaarus GPE 0.999995602846 Belarus B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Sofiya None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Bulgaari Bulgaari Bulgaari GPE 0.999996293515 Bulgaria B-LOC

Réewum Réewum_Cek Réewum_Cek GPE 0.999991038035 Czech_Republic B-LOC
Cek None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu None O
Jurbel None O
'' None O
' None O
benn None O
la None O
ci None O
diiwaani None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
. None O

Mi None O
ngi None O
yem None O
ci None O
diiwaani None O
Cees Diiwaanu_Cees Cees GPE 1.0 Thiès_Region B-LOC
ak None O
bu None O
Fatik Diiwaanu_Fatik Fatik GPE 1.0 Fatick_Region B-LOC
ci None O
bëj-gànnaaram None O
, None O
ci None O
bëj-saalumam None O
ci None O
diiwaani None O
Cees None O
ak None O
bu None O
Fatik None O
, None O
ci None O
penkoom None O
ci None O
diiwaani None O
Fatik None O
ak None O
bu None O
Luga Diiwaanu_Luga Luga GPE 1.0 Louga_Region B-LOC
, None O
ci None O
sowwam None O
ci None O
diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Cees diiwaanu_Cees GPE 1.0 Thiès_Region B-LOC
Cees None I-LOC
. None O

Diiwaan None O
bi None O
mi None O
ngi None O
nekk None O
tembe None O
fa None O
nguuru Bawol nguuru_bawol ORG 0.682608524192 Baol B-ORG
bawol None I-ORG
ga None O
nekkoon None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Kisinawu None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Moldaawi Moldaawi Moldaawi GPE 0.999994727044 Moldova B-LOC

Luksambuur Luksambuur Luksambuur GPE 0.999999999992 Luxembourg B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Prag None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
Réewum Réewum_Cek Réewum_Cek GPE 0.999991038035 Czech_Republic B-LOC
Cek None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Kiyew None O
'' None O
' None O
moy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Ukreen Ukreen Ukreen GPE 0.999986206506 Ukraine B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Kopenagen None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Danmaark Danmaark Danmaark GPE 0.999999999818 Denmark B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Warsaw None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Poloñ Poloñ Poloñ GPE 0.999995090538 Poland B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Dublin None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Irlaand Irlaand Irlaand GPE 0.99999999978 Republic_of_Ireland B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Riga None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Letóoni Letóoni Letóoni GPE 0.999998814392 Latvia B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Elsinki None O
'' None O
' None O
( None O
sv None O
: None O
' None O
'' None O
Helsingfors None O
'' None O
' None O
) None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Finlaand Finlaand Finlaand GPE 0.999994932457 Finland B-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Maatam Diiwaanu_Maatam GPE 1.0 Matam_Region B-LOC
Maatam None I-LOC
ak None O
bu None O
Luga Diiwaanu_Luga Luga GPE 1.0 Louga_Region B-LOC
ci None O
bëj-gànnaaram None O
; None O

Réewum None O
Gine Gine Gine GPE 0.922399934174 Guinea B-LOC
ci None O
bëj-saalumam None O
; None O

' None O
'' None O
Wilniyus None O
'' None O
' None O
Mooy None O
péyu None O
Réewum None O
Lituwaani Lituwaani Lituwaani GPE 0.999996763656 Lithuania B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Oslo None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
Mooy None O
péyu None O
Réewum None O
Noorwees Noorwees Noorwees GPE 0.999854200889 Norway B-LOC

Bosni Bosni Bosni GPE 0.922399934174 Bosnia_and_Herzegovina B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Baratislawa None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Eslowaaki Eslowaaki Eslowaaki GPE 0.999993309884 Slovakia B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Andorra None O
la None O
Vella None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Andoor Andoor Andoor GPE 0.999989201816 Andorra B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Tirana None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Albaani Albaani Albaani GPE 0.999996663787 Albania B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Bukarest None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Romaani Romaani Romaani GPE 0.999990867634 Romania B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Saarayego None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Bosni Bosni Bosni GPE 0.922399934174 Bosnia_and_Herzegovina B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Diwaanu None O
Luga None O
'' None O
' None O
benn None O
la None O
ci None O
14 None O
diwaani None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
. None O

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Ndar Diiwaanu_Ndar GPE 1.0 Saint-Louis_Region B-LOC
Ndar None I-LOC
, None O
ci None O
bëj-gànnaaram None O

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Maatam Diiwaanu_Maatam GPE 1.0 Matam_Region B-LOC
Maatam None I-LOC
ci None O
penkoom None O

' None O
'' None O
Waleta None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Malt Malt Malt GPE 1.0 Malta B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Sagreb None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Korwaasi Korwaasi Korwaasi GPE 0.999996710561 Croatia B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Skopje None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
Réewum Réewum_Maseduwaan Réewum_Maseduwaan GPE 0.999993345629 Republic_of_Macedonia B-LOC
Maseduwaan None I-LOC

Otris Otris Otris GPE 0.996472320534 Austria B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Podgora None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Montenegro Montenegro Montenegro GPE 0.999656339701 Montenegro B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Talin None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Estooni Estooni Estooni GPE 0.999997941033 Estonia B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
San None O
Maarino None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
Moy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
San San_Marino San_Marino GPE 0.999986075603 San_Marino B-LOC
Marino None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Belgrad None O
'' None O
' None O
Moy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Seerbi Seerbi Seerbi GPE 0.999992226335 Serbia B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Jubuljana None O
'' None O
' None O
Moy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Esloweeni Esloweeni Esloweeni GPE 0.999995415738 Slovenia B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Wadus None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
Mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Liechtenstein Liechtenstein Liechtenstein GPE 0.999999999597 Liechtenstein B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu None O
Maatam None O
'' None O
' None O
benn None O
la None O
ci None O
14 None O
diiwaani None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
. None O

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Ndar Diiwaanu_Ndar GPE 1.0 Saint-Louis_Region B-LOC
Ndar None I-LOC
ci None O
bëj-gànnaaram None O
; None O

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Luga Diiwaanu_Luga GPE 1.0 Louga_Region B-LOC
Luga None I-LOC
ci None O
sowwam None O
ak None O
ci None O
bëj-gànnaar-suwwam None O
; None O

Dexub Dexub_Senegaal Dexub_Senegaal GPE 0.999982599788 Senegal_River B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC
bi None O
, None O
fi None O
janook None O
réewum None O
Mali Mali Mali GPE 0.999997745646 Mali B-LOC
, None O
ci None O
penkoom None O
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Way Way Way GPE 0.820321732452 Music B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Watikaa None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Watikaa Watikaa Watikaa GPE 0.999998919962 Vatican_City B-LOC
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Girees Girees Girees GPE 0.999468851293 Greece B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Bern None O
'' None O
' None O
Mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Suwis Suwis Suwis GPE 0.999995552328 Switzerland B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Astaan None O
'' None O
' None O
Mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Kasakistaan Kasakistaan Kasakistaan GPE 0.999996070922 Kazakhstan B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Baku None O
'' None O
' None O
Mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Aserbayjaan Aserbayjaan Aserbayjaan GPE 0.999999999851 Azerbaijan B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Ankara None O
'' None O
' None O
Mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Tirki Tirki Tirki GPE 0.922399934174 Turkey B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Reykjawik None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Islaand Islaand Islaand GPE 0.999999999671 Iceland B-LOC
. None O

Diiwaan Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo GPE 0.99999348198 United_States B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Tibilisi None O
'' None O
' None O
Mooy None O
péyu None O
réewum None O
Jeoorji Jeoorji Jeoorji GPE 0.999994552331 Georgia_(country) B-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Belsik Belsik Belsik GPE 0.99999637399 Belgium B-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Mexe Mexe Mexe GPE 0.999999999381 Meckhe B-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Alaaji Alaaji_Maalik_Si Alaaji_Maalik_Si PER 0.999662428343 Malick_Sy B-PER
Maalik None I-PER
Si None I-PER

Saara Saara Saara GPE 0.999569142502 Sahara B-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Sharles Sharles_Degóol Sharles_Degóol PER 0.999999997035 Charles_de_Gaulle B-PER
Degóol None I-PER

Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Isipt Isipt Isipt GPE 0.999998703509 Egypt B-LOC

Ben None O
dekku None O
mi None O
ngi None O
nekk None O
Santiago Santiago_(Kap_Weer) Santiago_(Kap_Weer) GPE 0.999999999853 Santiago,_Cape_Verde B-LOC
( None I-LOC
Kap None I-LOC
Weer None I-LOC
) None I-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu None O
Kafrin None O
'' None O
' None O
benn None O
la None O
ci None O
14 None O
diiwaani None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
. None O

Bëer Bëer Bëer GPE 0.679699169051 Argyrosomus_regius B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu None O
Séeju None O
'' None O
' None O
benn None O
la None O
ci None O
14 None O
diiwaani None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu None O
Cees None O
'' None O
' None O
benn None O
la None O
ci None O
14 None O
diiwaan None O
yu None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
, None O
Féete None O
ci None O
penku None O
Réew None O
mi None O
, None O
wër None O
ndombo None O
Ndakaaru Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar_Region B-LOC
. None O

dëkkub None O
Cees Cees Cees GPE 0.999999776591 Thiès B-LOC
Mooy None O
Péeyu None O
diiwaan None O
bi None O
. None O

Doonte None O
diiwaan None O
bu None O
tuuti None O
la None O
soo None O
ko None O
méengalee None O
ak None O
yeneen None O
yi None O
, None O
waaye None O
mooy None O
ñaareelu None O
diiwaan None O
bi None O
ëppi None O
nit None O
, None O
ci None O
Réew None O
mi None O
, None O
ginnaaw None O
Ndakaaru Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar_Region B-LOC
. None O

Bokk None O
na None O
ci None O
diiwaan None O
yi None O
gën None O
a None O
yàgg None O
ci None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu None O
Kéedugu None O
'' None O
' None O
benn None O
la None O
ci None O
14 None O
diiwaani None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
. None O

Djabar Djabar Djabar GPE 0.679699169051 African_red_snapper B-LOC

Jasaan Jasaan Jasaan GPE 0.679699169051 Smalltooth_sawfish B-LOC

Diiwaan Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo GPE 0.99999348198 United_States B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC

San San_Marino_(péy) San_Marino_(péy) GPE 0.999999999993 City_of_San_Marino B-LOC
Marino None I-LOC
( None I-LOC
péy None I-LOC
) None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Wu-faraas None O
'' None O
' None O
, None O
mooy None O
làkk None O
wa None O
juddoo None O
ca None O
réewum None O
Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC
. None O

Goxub Goxub_Dottub_Bëj-saalum Goxub_Dottub_Bëj-saalum GPE 0.999981232676 Antarctica B-LOC
Dottub None I-LOC
Bëj-saalum None I-LOC

Ayiti Ayiti Ayiti GPE 0.999993568521 Haiti B-LOC

Diiwaan Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo GPE 0.99999348198 United_States B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC

Breesil Breesil Breesil GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

Angila Angila Angila GPE 0.989044130246 Anguilla B-LOC

Dunu Dunu_Christmas Dunu_Christmas GPE 0.999993314022 Christmas_Island B-LOC
Christmas None I-LOC

Premier Premier_League Premier_League ORG 0.999982633492 Premier_League B-ORG
League None I-ORG

Alex Alex_Ferguson Alex_Ferguson PER 0.999994838418 Alex_Ferguson B-PER
Ferguson None I-PER

Dunu Dunu_Buwet Dunu_Buwet GPE 0.999976022063 Bouvet_Island B-LOC
Buwet None I-LOC

Sili Sili Sili GPE 0.999989425747 Chile B-LOC

Dunu Dunu_Kokos Dunu_Kokos GPE 0.999998713076 Cocos_(Keeling)_Islands B-LOC
Kokos None I-LOC

Gine Gine_Bisaawóo Gine_Bisaawóo GPE 0.999997251857 Guinea-Bissau B-LOC
Bisaawóo None I-LOC

Groenlaand Groenlaand Groenlaand GPE 0.999999998561 Greenland B-LOC

Gine Gine Gine GPE 0.922399934174 Guinea B-LOC

Guwaatemala Guwaatemala Guwaatemala GPE 0.999987101048 Guatemala B-LOC

Guwaadalup Guwaadalup Guwaadalup GPE 1.0 Guadeloupe B-LOC

Duni Duni_Faarow Duni_Faarow GPE 0.999999972743 Faroe_Islands B-LOC
Faarow None I-LOC

Dunu Dunu_Norfolk Dunu_Norfolk ORG 0.946814421548 Norfolk_Island B-ORG
Norfolk None I-ORG

Ongiri Ongiri Ongiri GPE 0.999993411483 Hungary B-LOC

Mongoli Mongoli Mongoli GPE 0.999989145058 Mongolia B-LOC

Kamboodi Kamboodi Kamboodi GPE 0.999992714953 Cambodia B-LOC

Duni Duni_Virgin_(angalteer) Duni_Virgin_(angalteer) GPE 1.0 British_Virgin_Islands B-LOC
Virgin None I-LOC
( None I-LOC
angalteer None I-LOC
) None I-LOC

Jeoorji Jeoorji_gu_Bëj-saalum_ak_Duni_Islaand_yi_Bëj-saalum Jeoorji_gu_Bëj-saalum_ak_Duni_Islaand_yi_Bëj-saalum GPE 0.922399934174 South_Georgia_and_the_South_Sandwich_Islands B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Bëj-saalum None I-LOC
ak None I-LOC
Duni None I-LOC
Islaand None I-LOC
yi None I-LOC
Bëj-saalum None I-LOC

Duni Duni_Virgin_(angalteer) Duni_Virgin_(angalteer) GPE 1.0 British_Virgin_Islands B-LOC
Virgin None I-LOC
( None I-LOC
angalteer None I-LOC
) None I-LOC

Duni Duni_Virgin_(us) Duni_Virgin_(us) GPE 0.99999999999 United_States_Virgin_Islands B-LOC
Virgin None I-LOC
( None I-LOC
us None I-LOC
) None I-LOC

Libaa Libaa Libaa GPE 0.999994874838 Lebanon B-LOC

Jibraltaar Jibraltaar Jibraltaar GPE 0.999999999639 Gibraltar B-LOC

Bahrayni Bahrayni Bahrayni GPE 0.999996971777 Bahrain B-LOC

Réewum Réewum_Lawos Réewum_Lawos GPE 0.999992230797 Laos B-LOC
Lawos None I-LOC

Duni Duni_Marshall Duni_Marshall GPE 0.999999872649 Marshall_Islands B-LOC
Marshall None I-LOC

Xoolal None O
beneen None O
jukki None O
bi None O
tudd None O
Dottub Dottub_Bëj-gànnaar Dottub_Bëj-gànnaar GPE 0.992795187013 North_Pole B-LOC
Bëj-gànnaar None I-LOC

2010-2011 None O
Manchester Manchester_United Manchester_United ORG 0.999997942991 Manchester_United_F.C. B-ORG
United None I-ORG

2012-2013 None O
Manchester Manchester_United Manchester_United ORG 0.999997942991 Manchester_United_F.C. B-ORG
United None I-ORG

Diiwaan Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo GPE 0.99999348198 United_States B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC

Diiwaan Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo GPE 0.99999348198 United_States B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC

Sudaan Sudaan_(diiwaan) Sudaan_(diiwaan) GPE 0.999999999275 Sudan_(region) B-LOC
( None I-LOC
diiwaan None I-LOC
) None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Cees Diiwaanu_Cees GPE 1.0 Thiès_Region B-LOC
Cees None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Fatik Diiwaanu_Fatik GPE 1.0 Fatick_Region B-LOC
Fatik None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Njaaréem Diiwaanu_Njaaréem GPE 1.0 Diourbel_Region B-LOC
Njaaréem None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Kéedugu Diiwaanu_Kéedugu GPE 1.0 Kédougou_Region B-LOC
Kéedugu None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Kafrin Diiwaanu_Kafrin GPE 1.0 Kaffrine_Region B-LOC
Kafrin None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Kawlax Diiwaanu_Kawlax GPE 1.0 Kaolack_Region B-LOC
Kawlax None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Koldaa Diiwaanu_Koldaa GPE 1.0 Kolda_Region B-LOC
Koldaa None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Luga Diiwaanu_Luga GPE 1.0 Louga_Region B-LOC
Luga None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Maatam Diiwaanu_Maatam GPE 1.0 Matam_Region B-LOC
Maatam None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar_Region B-LOC
Ndakaaru None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Ndar Diiwaanu_Ndar GPE 1.0 Saint-Louis_Region B-LOC
Ndar None I-LOC

Su None O
nu None O
koy None O
xool None O
ci None O
lu None O
ëpp None O
mooy None O
nekk None O
Iraak Iraak Iraak GPE 0.999990857863 Iraq B-LOC
gu None O
tay None O
jii None O
. None O

Di None O
nañu None O
ci None O
boole None O
diiwaan None O
bi None O
nekk None O
ci None O
bëj-saalum None O
, None O
diggante None O
Tigre None O
ak None O
Ëfrat None O
( None O
ca None O
Iraak Iraak Iraak GPE 0.999990857863 Iraq B-LOC
gu None O
tay None O
) None O
. None O

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Séeju Diiwaanu_Séeju GPE 1.0 Sédhiou_Region B-LOC
Séeju None I-LOC

Réewum Réewum_Dominik Réewum_Dominik GPE 0.999989505525 Dominican_Republic B-LOC
Dominik None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Siggcoor Diiwaanu_Siggcoor GPE 1.0 Ziguinchor_Region B-LOC
Siggcoor None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Tambaakundaa Diiwaanu_Tambaakundaa GPE 1.0 Tambacounda_Region B-LOC
Tambaakundaa None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Njaaréem Diiwaanu_Njaaréem GPE 1.0 Diourbel_Region B-LOC
Njaaréem None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Njaaréem Diiwaanu_Njaaréem GPE 1.0 Diourbel_Region B-LOC
Njaaréem None I-LOC

Burkinaa Burkinaa_Faaso Burkinaa_Faaso GPE 0.999997745646 Burkina_Faso B-LOC
Faaso None I-LOC

Gineg Gineg_yamoo Gineg_yamoo GPE 0.999995565381 Equatorial_Guinea B-LOC
yamoo None I-LOC

Tuubaa Tuubaa Tuubaa GPE 1.0 Touba,_Senegal B-LOC

Papuwaasi-Gine-Gu-Bees Papuwaasi-Gine-Gu-Bees Papuwaasi-Gine-Gu-Bees GPE 0.999993796375 Papua_New_Guinea B-LOC

Dexub Dexub_Senegaal Dexub_Senegaal GPE 0.999982599788 Senegal_River B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Tugal Tugal Tugal GPE 1.0 Europe B-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Kap Kap_Weert Kap_Weert GPE 0.999999999794 Cape_Verde B-LOC
Weert None I-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Kodiwaar Kodiwaar Kodiwaar GPE 0.978326487531 Ivory_Coast B-LOC

Moroni Moroni Moroni GPE 1.0 Moroni,_Comoros B-LOC

Ay None O
dàttam None O
ñi None O
ngi None O
bàyyikoo None O
ci None O
dundiin None O
gu None O
metti None O
gi None O
ñu None O
nekkee None O
woon None O
, None O
dalee None O
ca None O
seeni None O
maam None O
ba None O
ci None O
jamono None O
yi None O
muy None O
juddu None O
, None O
woy None O
yañu None O
daan None O
def None O
ca None O
tool None O
ya None O
daan None O
ca None O
naqarlu None O
seenug None O
nekkiin None O
, None O
ak None O
daan None O
ca None O
fattali None O
seenug None O
jóge None O
Afrig Afrig Afrig GPE 1.0 Africa B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Nairobi None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Keeñaa Keeñaa Keeñaa GPE 0.999996929882 Kenya B-LOC
di None O
itam None O
dëkk None O
bi None O
fa None O
gën None O
a None O
rëy None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Lilongwe None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Malawi Malawi Malawi GPE 0.999997827871 Malawi B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Kampala None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Ugandaa Ugandaa Ugandaa GPE 0.999935749545 Uganda B-LOC
. None O

Réewu None O
Afrig None O
: None O
Gànnaar Gànnaar Gànnaar GPE 0.999998358563 Mauritania B-LOC
- None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Asmara None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Eritere Eritere Eritere GPE 0.999992862604 Eritrea B-LOC
di None O
itam None O
dëkk None O
ba None O
fa None O
gën None O
a None O
rëy None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Jibuti None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réew None O
mi None O
tudd None O
moom None O
itam None O
Jibuti Jibuti Jibuti GPE 0.999997722281 Djibouti B-LOC
, None O
am None O
na None O
542000 None O
way-dëkk None O
te None O
rëye None O
630 None O

' None O
'' None O
Addis-Abeba None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Ecoopi Ecoopi Ecoopi GPE 0.999992867998 Ethiopia B-LOC
, None O
mi None O
ngi None O
nekk None O
ci None O
diggu None O
dëkk None O
bi None O
, None O
nekk None O
cig None O
joor None O
ju None O
kawe None O
ci None O
diggante None O
2300 None O
ak None O
2600 None O
metar None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Kigali None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Ruwandaa Ruwandaa Ruwandaa GPE 0.999998328267 Rwanda B-LOC

Maputo Maputo Maputo GPE 1.0 Maputo B-LOC
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Mosambik Mosambik Mosambik GPE 0.999997247099 Mozambique B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Mogadisu None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Somali Somali Somali GPE 0.999999999986 Somalia B-LOC
. None O

Ceññeer-mbej Ceññeer-mbej Ceññeer-mbej ORG 0.997244032626 Radio_broadcasting B-ORG
: None O

' None O
'' None O
Antananariwo None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Madagaskaar Madagaskaar Madagaskaar GPE 0.999999999955 Madagascar B-LOC
. None O

Image None O
: None O
Antananarivo04.jpg|Ab None O
aji-xare None O
bu None O
dee None O
ngir None O
Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC

Li None O
ëppoon None O
ci None O
seeni None O
wax None O
ci None O
aadaay None O
Afrig Afrig Afrig GPE 1.0 Africa B-LOC
ak None O
Jamayka Jamayka Jamayka GPE 0.999994364924 Jamaica B-LOC
la None O
doon None O
jóge None O
. None O

Ci None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
rap None O
teel None O
na None O
fee None O
àggsi None O
, None O
ci None O
ndoorteelu None O
ati None O
juroom-ñett None O
yi None O
la None O
gangoor None O
yi None O
njëkk None O
juddu None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Yaunde None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Kamerun Kamerun Kamerun GPE 0.99999847838 Cameroon B-LOC
, None O

' None O
'' None O
Bangi None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
Réewum Réewum_Diggu_Afrig Réewum_Diggu_Afrig GPE 0.999996846848 Central_African_Republic B-LOC
Diggu None I-LOC
Afrig None I-LOC
, None O
way-dëkkam None O
ñoo None O
ngi None O
koy None O
xayma None O
ci None O
622 None O
800 None O
ci None O
2003 None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Njamena None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Cadd Cadd Cadd GPE 0.922399934174 Chad B-LOC
, None O
di None O
itam None O
dëkk None O
ba None O
fa None O
gën None O
a None O
rëy None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Lusaka None O
'' None O
' None O
mi None O
ngi None O
nekk None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Saambi Saambi Saambi GPE 0.999997827871 Zambia B-LOC
ci None O
bi None O
muy None O
am None O
tembteem None O
ci None O
1964 None O
, None O
Sancaan None O
yu None O
waa-tugal Tugal waa-tugal GPE 1.0 Europe B-LOC
yee None O
ko None O
sos None O
ci None O
atum None O
1905 None O
ci None O
ba None O
ñuy None O
defar None O
yoonu None O
weñ None O
wi None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Kinshasa None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Kongóo-Kinshasa Kongóo-Kinshasa Kongóo-Kinshasa GPE 0.999997062197 Democratic_Republic_of_the_Congo B-LOC
. None O

Buruundi Buruundi Buruundi GPE 0.999995626681 Burundi B-LOC

FI None O
Burundi None O
féete None O
ci None O
Buruundi Buruundi Buruundi GPE 0.999995626681 Burundi B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Bujumbura None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Buruundi Buruundi Buruundi GPE 0.999995626681 Burundi B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Wiktoria None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Seysel Seysel Seysel GPE 0.999999999766 Seychelles B-LOC
, None O
mooy None O
dëkk None O
bi None O
ëpp None O
way-dëkk None O
ci None O
dun None O
bi None O

' None O
'' None O
Luiz None O
Felipe None O
de None O
Camargo None O
e None O
Almeida None O
Neto None O
'' None O
' None O
( None O
1 None O
agosto None O
1960 None O
, None O
Rio None O
de None O
Janeiro None O
) None O
: None O
Breesilian Breesil Breesilian GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Nha None O
Trang None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Bien None O
Hoa None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Mohammed Mohammed Mohammed PER 0.999991166281 Muhammad B-PER

' None O
'' None O
Bà None O
Rịa None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Réewum Réewum_Popileer_bu_Siin Réewum_Popileer_bu_Siin GPE 0.999999167165 China B-LOC
Popileer None I-LOC
bu None I-LOC
Siin None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Phan None O
Thiet None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Ben None O
Tre None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Thanh None O
Hoa None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC
. None O

Noorwees Noorwees Noorwees GPE 0.999854200889 Norway B-LOC

Noorwees Noorwees Noorwees GPE 0.999854200889 Norway B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Taís None O
Bianca None O
Gama None O
de None O
Araújo None O
Ramos None O
'' None O
' None O
( None O
25 None O
November None O
1978 None O
, None O
Rio None O
de None O
Janeiro None O
) None O
: None O
Breesilian Breesil Breesilian GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Nicete None O
Xavier None O
Miessa None O
'' None O
' None O
( None O
7 None O
January None O
1933 None O
, None O
Niterói None O
) None O
: None O
Breesilian Breesil Breesilian GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

Tugal Tugal Tugal GPE 1.0 Europe B-LOC
ak None O
Oseyaani Oseyaani Oseyaani GPE 1.0 Oceania B-LOC
rekk None O
la None O
gën None O
a None O
réy None O
. None O

Goxub Goxub_Dottub_Bëj-gànnaar Goxub_Dottub_Bëj-gànnaar GPE 0.992795187013 Arctic B-LOC
Dottub None I-LOC
Bëj-gànnaar None I-LOC

Dottub Dottub_Bëj-saalum Dottub_Bëj-saalum GPE 0.992795187013 South_Pole B-LOC
Bëj-saalum None I-LOC

Dottub Dottub_Bëj-gànnaar Dottub_Bëj-gànnaar GPE 0.992795187013 North_Pole B-LOC
Bëj-gànnaar None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Niccolò None O
Cusano None O
University None O
'' None O
' None O
- None O
Unicusano None O
ab None O
university None O
Rom Rom Rom GPE 1.0 Rome B-LOC
, None O
Itaali Itaali Itaali GPE 0.999994576668 Italy B-LOC
. None O

Noorwees Noorwees Noorwees GPE 0.999854200889 Norway B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Siligo None O
'' None O
' None O
ca None O
réewum None O
Itaali Itaali Itaali GPE 0.999994576668 Italy B-LOC
. None O

Diiwaani Diiwaani_Senegaal Diiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.999977872861 Regions_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC
( None O
Régions None O
du None O
Sénégal None O
) None O

Tundi Tundi_Senegaal Tundi_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC
( None O
Département None O
du None O
Sénégal None O
) None O

Noorwees Noorwees Noorwees GPE 0.999854200889 Norway B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Ba None O
Đồn None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
The None O
Doors None O
'' None O
' None O
bi None O
Diiwaan Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo GPE 0.99999348198 United_States B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC
rock None O
buum None O
. None O

Seerbi Seerbi Seerbi GPE 0.999992226335 Serbia B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Trojany None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
Poloñ Poloñ Poloñ GPE 0.999995090538 Poland B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Budka None O
Suflera None O
'' None O
' None O
bi None O
Poloñ Poloñ Poloñ GPE 0.999995090538 Poland B-LOC
rock None O
buum None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Bochotnica None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Poloñ Poloñ Poloñ GPE 0.999995090538 Poland B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Ronald None O
Wilson None O
Reagan None O
'' None O
' None O
( None O
1911-2004 None O
) None O
: None O
njiitull None O
Diiwaan Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo GPE 0.99999348198 United_States B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC
yi None O
( None O
1981-1989 None O
) None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Baynuk None O
'' None O
' None O
, None O
benn None O
waaso None O
la None O
, None O
ci None O
reewum None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Saw Saw_Tome_ak_Preesip Saw_Tome_ak_Preesip GPE 0.922399934174 São_Tomé_and_Príncipe B-LOC
Tome None I-LOC
ak None I-LOC
Preesip None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Yoro None O
Booli None O
Jaw None O
'' None O
' None O
( None O
Yoro None O
Jaw None O
) None O
, None O
taarixkat None O
la None O
woon None O
ca None O
cosaanu None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
, None O
gane None O
adduna None O
1847 None O
, None O
te None O
dee None O
ca None O
atum None O
1919 None O
. None O

Bokk None O
naa None O
ci None O
ñu None O
jëkk None O
nettali None O
cossanu None O
wolof None O
yi None O
, None O
ci None O
kallamu None O
nasaraan None O
, None O
ca None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
. None O

Li None O
yepp None O
xewoon None O
naa None O
ci None O
dundu None O
Yoro None O
Jaw None O
ca None O
Ndar Ndar Ndar GPE 0.999999999958 Saint-Louis,_Senegal B-LOC
, None O
diggante None O
atum None O
1856 None O
ak None O
1860 None O
, None O
mu None O
gén None O
ci None O
, None O
ca None O
tegu None O
, None O
tubaap None O
yi None O
teg None O
ko None O
li None O
ñu None O
wax None O
''chef None O
de None O
canton None O
'' None O
ca None O
Waalo None O
, None O
ci None O
dëkk None O
bu None O
tuddu None O
Foos None O
ak None O
Xuuma None O
tamit None O
, None O
ca None O
atum None O
1860 None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Laman None O
'' None O
' None O
, None O
walla None O
' None O
'' None O
lamaan None O
'' None O
' None O
, None O
benn None O
tur None O
la None O
, None O
ñu None O
ko None O
daan None O
joxe None O
ñu None O
yorewoon None O
suuf None O
si None O
, None O
ci None O
jamono None O
ju None O
yagg None O
ya None O
, None O
ca None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
. None O

Ba None O
jamono None O
Jolof Jolof Jolof GPE 0.795338880767 Jolof_Empire B-LOC
uuf None O
nguur None O
yi None O
yepp None O
, None O
laman None O
yi None O
nekoon None O
ca None O
nguur None O
yi None O
, None O
dootuñuwoon None O
ay None O
buur None O
, None O
ndax None O
buur-ba None O
Jolof None O
rekk None O
moo None O
nekkon None O
buur None O
( None O
buur None O
fari None O
) None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Kaabu None O
'' None O
' None O
, None O
benn None O
nguur None O
la None O
woon None O
, None O
ca None O
bëj None O
saalumu None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
ak None O
kawu None O
Gine Gine_Bisaawóo Gine_Bisaawóo GPE 0.999997251857 Guinea-Bissau B-LOC
Bisaawóo None I-LOC
. None O

Tey None O
, None O
mengoo None O
na None O
ak None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Séeju Diiwaanu_Séeju GPE 1.0 Sédhiou_Region B-LOC
Séeju None I-LOC
, None O

Kolda Diiwaanu_Koldaa Kolda GPE 1.0 Kolda_Region B-LOC
, None O
ak None O
li None O
ko None O
wër None O
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Otris Otris Otris GPE 0.996472320534 Austria B-LOC

Jangoroy None O
yaram-wu-tàng None O
ju None O
Ebola None O
ñoo None O
ngi None O
ko None O
njëkkeen None O
gis None O
ca None O
Sudaan Sudaan Sudaan GPE 0.99999945476 Sudan B-LOC
ak None O
ca None O
Kongóo Kongóo-Kinshasa Kongóo GPE 0.999997062197 Democratic_Republic_of_the_Congo B-LOC
. None O

Naka-jekk None O
njàngoro None O
ji None O
dafa None O
daan None O
faral None O
di None O
yem None O
rek None O
ci None O
yenn None O
barab None O
yu None O
ndaw None O
yu None O
beru None O
ci None O
yenn None O
réewi None O
Afrig Afrig Afrig GPE 1.0 Africa B-LOC
yu None O
ron-sahara None O
yi None O
. None O

Wàllante None O
gi None O
gën None O
a None O
réy None O
gu None O
Ebola None O
moo None O
ngi None O
ame None O
ci None O
ndoorteelu None O
2014 None O
te None O
barab None O
yi None O
mu None O
gën None O
a None O
tasee None O
ñooy None O
réew None O
yu None O
Gine Gine Gine GPE 0.922399934174 Guinea B-LOC
, None O
Siraa Siraa_Leyoon Siraa_Leyoon GPE 0.999998178618 Sierra_Leone B-LOC
Leyoon None I-LOC
, None O
Libeeria Libeeria Libeeria GPE 0.999994592957 Liberia B-LOC
a None O
Niseeria Niseeria Niseeria GPE 0.999998094206 Nigeria B-LOC
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Leopool Leopool_Sedaar_Sengoor Leopool_Sedaar_Sengoor PER 0.999999999992 Léopold_Sédar_Senghor B-PER
Sedaar None I-PER
Sengoor None I-PER

redirection None O
Leopool Leopool_Sedaar_Sengoor Leopool_Sedaar_Sengoor PER 0.999999999992 Léopold_Sédar_Senghor B-PER
Sedaar None I-PER
Sengoor None I-PER

Elimas Elimas Elimas PER 0.483590280508 Elymas B-PER

Xaaj None O
bu None O
yaa None O
bu None O
taariixu None O
nit None O
njëkk None O
sosug None O
mbind None O
, None O
ci None O
xayma None O
, None O
mi None O
ngi None O
door None O
mat None O
na None O
200 None O
junni None O
at None O
, None O
ba None O
jëmm None O
ji None O
njëkk None O
jees None O
man None O
a None O
nattanleek None O
nitu None O
tay None O
jii None O
feeñee None O
ci None O
Afrig Afrig_gu_Bëj-saalum Afrig_gu_Bëj-saalum GPE 0.999997104528 South_Africa B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Bëj-saalum None I-LOC
. None O

Fey None O
na None O
Balaam Balaam Balaam ORG 0.646888881052 Balaam B-ORG
, None O
ngir None O
mu None O
rëbbal None O
ko None O
bànni None O
Israyil None O
. None O

Dafa None O
digal None O
buuru None O
Mowab None O
Balag Balag Balag PER 0.947931906784 Balak B-PER
, None O
ñu None O
jéema None O
boole None O
waa None O
Israyil None O
ak None O
jaamu None O
xërëm None O
. None O

Way Way Way GPE 0.820321732452 Music B-LOC

Betani Betani_bu_Yerusalem Betani_ca_wetu_Yerusalem GPE 1.0 Al-Eizariya B-LOC
ca None I-LOC
wetu None I-LOC
Yerusalem None I-LOC

Betani Betani_bu_Yurdan Betani_ca_penku_dexu_Yurdan GPE 0.768646283882 Bethabara B-LOC
ca None I-LOC
penku None I-LOC
dexu None I-LOC
Yurdan None I-LOC

Sorewul None O
Betani Betani Betani GPE 0.760351571191 Bethany_(biblical_village) B-LOC
. None O

Dëkku None O
Daawuda Daawuda Daawuda PER 0.999999996272 David B-PER
la None O
. None O

Baayu None O
Balaam Balaam Balaam ORG 0.646888881052 Balaam B-ORG
la None O
woon None O
. None O

Tirki Tirki Tirki GPE 0.922399934174 Turkey B-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Kawlax Diiwaanu_Kawlax GPE 1.0 Kaolack_Region B-LOC
Kawlax None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Tambaakundaa Diiwaanu_Tambaakundaa GPE 1.0 Tambacounda_Region B-LOC
Tambaakundaa None I-LOC

Yéesu-kristaa Yéesu-kristaa Yéesu-kristaa PER 0.999970541367 Jesus B-PER
. None O

Bis None O
gan None O
dikkal None O
na None O
ko None O
di None O
kilafa None O
gu None O
bawoo None O
ci None O
biti None O
, None O
bi None O
muy None O
wax None O
ak None O
moom None O
ci None O
lu None O
aju None O
ci None O
tànnéefi None O
njiit None O
yu None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yu None O
waroon None O
a None O
am None O
ca None O
jamono None O
jooja None O
, None O
gan None O
ga None O
daal None O
di None O
koy None O
laaj None O
kan None O
la None O
faral None O
ci None O
lawax None O
yi None O
( None O
les None O
candidats None O
) None O
? None O

S None O
Saaliwu None O
ak None O
doomam None O
S None O
Mustafaa None O
Saaliwu None O
Ka None O
njiitul None O
Iraan None O
la None O
woon None O
Rafsanjaani None O
ci None O
nemmeeku None O
bu None O
mu None O
defsi None O
woon None O
Tuubaa Tuubaa Tuubaa GPE 1.0 Touba,_Senegal B-LOC

«Jural-leen None O
dee None O
, None O
tabaxal None O
mbàbb» None O
'' None O
' None O
, None O
muy None O
ci None O
maanaa None O
lu None O
fi None O
waay None O
jur None O
dee None O
dina None O
digg None O
leegi None O
ne None O
ko None O
fuuf None O
, None O
lu None O
ngéen None O
tabax None O
it None O
day None O
mbàbb None O
leegi None O
, None O
kii None O
nag None O
lii None O
la None O
tegoon None O
ci None O
ron None O
bëtam None O
, None O
jëfam None O
jépp None O
it None O
Yàlla None O
la None O
ak None O
lu None O
ci None O
jëm None O
, None O
misaal None O
mi None O
kenn None O
la None O
woon None O
ku None O
àddinaadi None O
, None O
te None O
teewul None O
mu None O
sos None O
fi None O
lol None O
maseesu None O
ko None O
fee None O
sos None O
ci None O
ay None O
sémb None O
yu None O
mag None O
, None O
xoolal None O
li None O
mu None O
fi None O
bàyyi None O
ci None O
xaalis None O
, None O
tollu None O
na None O
ci None O
lu None O
jege None O
17 None O
milyaar None O
, None O
ñeel None O
naal None O
yu None O
aju None O
ci None O
Dëkkub None O
S None O
Tuubaa None O
bi None O
, None O
te None O
loolu None O
masut None O
a None O
am None O
ci None O
taariixu None O
yoon None O
wi None O
, None O
la None O
ko None O
dale None O
ca None O
Waajur None O
wa None O
ba None O
ci None O
fii None O
ma None O
la None O
koy None O
waxe None O
, None O
te None O
loolu None O
bokkul None O
ak None O
li None O
mu None O
fi None O
jot None O
a None O
liggéey None O
ci None O
alali None O
boppam None O
, None O
te None O
loola None O
gën None O
jaa None O
néew None O
mu None O
weesu None O
7 None O
milyaar None O
, None O
lu None O
sakkan None O
ciy None O
kër None O
S None O
Tuubaa None O
sosoo None O
na None O
ciy None O
loxoom None O
, None O
waxuma None O
la None O
li None O
sosu None O
ciy None O
jumaa None O
aki None O
jàkka None O
cig None O
ayam None O
te None O
ñuy None O
yu None O
réy None O
te None O
taaru None O
. None O

'' None O
Espargos Espargos Espargos GPE 0.999999999999 Espargos B-LOC
'' None O
' None O

' None O
'' None O
Yéesu-kristaa None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
Yéesu-kristaa Yéesu-kristaa Yéesu-kristaa PER 0.999970541367 Jesus B-PER
, None O
baat None O
bi None O
soppiku None O
nekk None O
suux None O
, None O
faatu None O
ci None O
cruaa None O
bi None O
ngir None O
man None O
a None O
jënd None O
bakkaar None O
yi None O
, None O
mu None O
feeñaat None O
ci None O
ñetteelu None O
bes None O
bi None O
dal None O
di None O
yéek None O
asamaan None O
. None O

Ca None O
jamono None O
nguuru None O
Kuus None O
amoon None O
, None O
tey None O
di None O
nekk None O
wa None O
Sudaan Sudaan Sudaan GPE 0.99999945476 Sudan B-LOC
, None O
nit None O
ñoo None O
fa None O
nekkoon None O
, None O
dañu None O
daan None O
nekk None O
ca None O
diine None O
yu None O
jekk None O
am None O
ca None O
adduna None O
, None O
ci None O
li None O
taarixkat None O
wonee None O
. None O

Bammel None O
bu None O
Méroé None O
, None O
Sudaan Sudaan Sudaan GPE 0.99999945476 Sudan B-LOC

Yoruba None O
yi None O
Ca None O
Niseeria Niseeria Niseeria GPE 0.999998094206 Nigeria B-LOC
: None O
''Olodumare None O
'' None O

Wa None O
Ecoopi Ecoopi Ecoopi GPE 0.999992867998 Ethiopia B-LOC
: None O
''Waqa None O
'' None O

*35 None O
' None O
'' None O
tund Tundi_Senegaal tund GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
'' None O
' None O
ñoom None O
ci None O
séen None O
bopp None O
dañu None O
leen None O
a None O
séddale None O
ci None O
92 None O
' None O
'' None O
ndiiwaan Ndiiwaani_Senegaal ndiiwaan GPE 0.733996404965 Arrondissements_of_Senegal B-LOC
'' None O
' None O
. None O

Ndakaaru Ndakaaru Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar B-LOC
, None O
ci None O
misaal None O
, None O
yor None O
na None O
ci None O
19 None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar_Region B-LOC
Ndakaaru None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

Ndakaaru Ndakaaru Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar B-LOC

Tëngéej Tëngéej Tëngéej GPE 0.999999999381 Rufisque B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Njaaréem Diiwaanu_Njaaréem GPE 1.0 Diourbel_Region B-LOC
Njaaréem None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Fatik Diiwaanu_Fatik GPE 1.0 Fatick_Region B-LOC
Fatik None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

Fatik Fatik Fatik GPE 0.999982434571 Fatick B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Kawlax Diiwaanu_Kawlax GPE 1.0 Kaolack_Region B-LOC
Kawlax None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Koldaa Diiwaanu_Koldaa GPE 1.0 Kolda_Region B-LOC
Koldaa None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Luga Diiwaanu_Luga GPE 1.0 Louga_Region B-LOC
Luga None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

Luga Luga Luga ORG 0.996899991992 Louga_Department B-ORG

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Maatam Diiwaanu_Maatam GPE 1.0 Matam_Region B-LOC
Maatam None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

Maatam Maatam Maatam GPE 0.999999770332 Matam,_Senegal B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Ndar Diiwaanu_Ndar GPE 1.0 Saint-Louis_Region B-LOC
Ndar None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

Ndar Ndar Ndar GPE 0.999999999958 Saint-Louis,_Senegal B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Tambaakundaa Diiwaanu_Tambaakundaa GPE 1.0 Tambacounda_Region B-LOC
Tambaakundaa None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Cees Diiwaanu_Cees GPE 1.0 Thiès_Region B-LOC
Cees None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

Mbuur Mbuur Mbuur GPE 0.999999999381 M'Bour B-LOC

Cees Cees Cees GPE 0.999999776591 Thiès B-LOC

Mexe Mexe Mexe GPE 0.999999999381 Meckhe B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Siggcoor Diiwaanu_Siggcoor GPE 1.0 Ziguinchor_Region B-LOC
Siggcoor None I-LOC
'' None O
' None O

Diiwaani Diiwaani_Senegaal Diiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.999977872861 Regions_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Tundi Tundi_Senegaal Tundi_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Ndiiwaani Ndiiwaani_Senegaal Ndiiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Arrondissements_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Diiwaani Diiwaani_Senegaal Diiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.999977872861 Regions_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Ndiiwaani Ndiiwaani_Senegaal Ndiiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Arrondissements_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Tundi Tundi_Senegaal Tundi_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Ndiiwaani Ndiiwaani_Senegaal Ndiiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Arrondissements_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Almaañ Almaañ Almaañ GPE 0.999994565441 Germany B-LOC
njëkk None O
xarey None O
Napoleon None O
yi None O
, None O
dafa None O
séddaliku None O
woon None O
ci None O
lu None O
jege None O
ñatti None O
téemeer None O
ak None O
juroom None O
benn None O
fukki None O
diiwaan None O
( None O
360 None O
diiwaan None O
) None O
, None O
yépp None O
it None O
ci None O
ron None O
imbraatóor None O
gu None O
Otris None O
lañu None O
nekkoon None O
, None O
walla None O
li None O
ñuy None O
tudde None O
' None O
'' None O
Imbraatóor None O
gu None O
Rom None O
gu None O
sell None O
'' None O
' None O
gi None O
. None O

Daal None O
di None O
jawali None O
ca None O
nguurug None O
Brusiya None O
, None O
gi None O
nga None O
xam None O
ne None O
jàmmaarloo None O
woon None O
na’ak None O
ñoom None O
cig None O
njàmmaar None O
ak None O
fit None O
, None O
waaye None O
Napoleon None O
moom None O
mujj None O
na None O
ko None O
noot None O
, None O
te None O
gañe None O
ko None O
ci None O
mujj None O
gi None O
, None O
ca None O
' None O
'' None O
xareb None O
Yena None O
ba None O
'' None O
' None O
, None O
atum None O
1806g None O
, None O
daal None O
di None O
teg None O
loxo None O
péeyam None O
ba None O
Berlin Berlin Berlin GPE 1.0 Berlin B-LOC
. None O

Ginnaaw None O
bi None O
mu None O
nekkal None O
réewam None O
ca None O
Paris.foofee None O
la None O
ko None O
' None O
'' None O
William None O
mu None O
njëkk None O
'' None O
' None O
mi None O
doon None O
jiite None O
Brusiya None O
woowe None O
woon None O
mu None O
juge None O
Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC
, None O
ngir None O
jiite-si None O
njiitug None O
jawrin None O
gi None O
ci None O
Brusiya None O
. None O

Dëppoo None O
woon None O
na None O
ak None O
Imbratóor None O
bi None O
Napoleon None O
III None O
, None O
imbraatóoru None O
Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC
, None O
moom None O
itam None O
, None O
ngir None O
mu None O
seetaan None O
kook None O
Otris None O
, None O
bañ None O
cee None O
dugal None O
loxoom None O
, None O
li None O
mu None O
koy None O
faye None O
ci None O
loolu None O
nag None O
mooy None O
bàyyi None O
kook None O
yenn None O
moomeel None O
yi None O
ci None O
diiwaanub None O
Rayn None O
. None O

Bu None O
ag None O
dimblante None O
gu None O
am None O
solo None O
amee None O
, None O
walla None O
gu None O
xare None O
ci None O
diggante None O
Riisi None O
ak None O
Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC
, None O
ñaari None O
réew None O
yii None O
tapoo None O
de None O
war None O
nanoo None O
ànd None O
liggéey None O
ngir None O
xeex None O
loolu None O
. None O

Ag None O
dëppoog None O
cofeel None O
sosu None O
na None O
ci None O
diggante None O
Brëtaañ None O
ak None O
Sapoŋ Sapoŋ Sapoŋ GPE 0.999984323433 Japan B-LOC
ci None O
atum None O
1902g None O
, None O
lii None O
la None O
yaxal None O
: None O

Faraas None O
moom None O
tam None O
nangul None O
Brëtaañ None O
teg None O
gi None O
mu None O
teg None O
loxo None O
Isipt Isipt Isipt GPE 0.999998703509 Egypt B-LOC
ci None O
atum None O
1882 None O

Déggoo None O
ci None O
ni None O
nuy None O
séddoo None O
barabi None O
sañ-sañ None O
yi None O
ci None O
Iraan Iraan Iraan GPE 0.999989905078 Iran B-LOC
, None O
ba None O
mu None O
des None O
fa None O
benn None O
barab None O
rekk None O
bu None O
temb None O
ca None O
digg None O
ba None O
ñu None O
bàyyil None O
ko None O
fa None O
Shaah None O
ba None O
, None O
ginaaw None O
bi None O
Riisi None O
jëlee None O
wàll None O
gu None O
bëj-gànnaar None O
gi None O
, None O
Brëtaañ None O
jël None O
gu None O
bëj-saalum None O
gi None O
. None O

Saxal None O
ya None O
juddoo None O
ca None O
ndaje None O
ma None O
nag None O
njariñul None O
Faraas None O
la None O
gënoon None O
a None O
nekk None O
, None O
ndax None O
réew None O
ya None O
fa None O
daje None O
woon None O
dañoo None O
dëppoo None O
woon None O
ci None O
nangul None O
Maraakes None O
ag None O
tembam None O
waaye None O
feetale None O
Faraas None O
wàllug None O
kaaraange None O
ga None O
ak None O
sàmm None O
njabootug None O
Tugal Tugal Tugal GPE 1.0 Europe B-LOC
ga None O
fa None O
nekkoon None O
. None O

Siri Siri Siri GPE 0.999994189148 Syria B-LOC

Lat Lat_Joor Lat_Joor PER 0.994295226107 Lat-Dior B-PER
Joor None I-PER

Gàmbi Gàmbi Gàmbi GPE 0.999998160509 The_Gambia B-LOC

Yuusu Yuusu_Nduur Yuusu_Nduur PER 0.999999963615 Youssou_N'Dour B-PER
Nduur None I-PER

Bëer Bëer Bëer GPE 0.679699169051 Argyrosomus_regius B-LOC

Lii None O
mooy None O
limub None O
njiitl None O
réewum None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
la None O
ko None O
dale None O
ca None O
ba None O
mu None O
tembee None O
ca None O
Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC
4 None O
Awril None O
1960 None O
. None O

Ndiiwani None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC

Tund Tundi_Senegaal Tund GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
la None O
ndiiwaan None O
la None O

Tunduw Tunduw_Ndakaaru Tunduw_Ndakaaru ORG 0.996899991992 Dakar_Department B-ORG
Ndakaaru None I-ORG

Tund Tundi_Senegaal Tund GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
la None O
ndiiwaan None O
la None O

Gannaaw None O
dogaat None O
ga None O
waraaloon None O
juddug None O
Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Maatam Diiwaanu_Maatam GPE 1.0 Matam_Region B-LOC
Maatam None I-LOC
, None O
tund None O
wi None O
, None O
wenn None O
ndiiwaan None O
rekk None O
la None O
am None O
muy None O
bu None O

Tund Tundi_Senegaal Tund GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
la None O
ndiiwaan None O
la None O

Diiwaani Diiwaani_Senegaal Diiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.999977872861 Regions_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Tundi Tundi_Senegaal Tundi_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Ndiiwaani Ndiiwaani_Senegaal Ndiiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Arrondissements_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Oiapoque None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
dëkku None O
Breesil Breesil Breesil GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

Djabar Djabar Djabar GPE 0.679699169051 African_red_snapper B-LOC

Yokkug None O
nit None O
ñi None O
dëkk None O
ci None O
Ndakaaru Ndakaaru Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar B-LOC
moo None O
dem None O
ba None O
àgg None O
ci None O
benn None O
dayoo None O
bi None O
, None O
ba None O
tax None O
genn None O
kilifag None O
dëkk None O
rekk None O
manatu None O
koo None O
yor None O
, None O
tax None O
sosug None O
geneen None O
nekkte None O
gu None O
gën None O
a None O
suufe None O
waroon None O
. None O

Ndakaaru Ndakaaru Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar B-LOC
: None O
19 None O

Tëngéej Tëngéej Tëngéej GPE 0.999999999381 Rufisque B-LOC
: None O
3 None O

Cees Cees Cees GPE 0.999999776591 Thiès B-LOC
: None O
3 None O

Diiwaani Diiwaani_Senegaal Diiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.999977872861 Regions_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Tundi Tundi_Senegaal Tundi_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Ndiiwaani Ndiiwaani_Senegaal Ndiiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Arrondissements_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Bëer Bëer Bëer GPE 0.679699169051 Argyrosomus_regius B-LOC

Fëtt Fëtt Fëtt GPE 0.679699169051 Pseudotolithus B-LOC

Ngaté Ngaté_bu_digen Ngaté_bu_digen GPE 0.679699169051 Diplodus_vulgaris B-LOC
bu None I-LOC
digen None I-LOC

Jasaan Jasaan Jasaan GPE 0.679699169051 Smalltooth_sawfish B-LOC

Fëtt Fëtt Fëtt GPE 0.679699169051 Pseudotolithus B-LOC

Finlaand Finlaand Finlaand GPE 0.999994932457 Finland B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Coronel None O
Fabriciano None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
dëkku None O
Breesil Breesil Breesil GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Al None O
Bayda None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Libi Libi Libi GPE 0.999999999984 Libya B-LOC
. None O

Ci None O
Jëmm Jëmm Jëmm GPE 0.982273304022 Physics B-LOC
, None O
' None O
'' None O
baraay None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
delluwaay None O
la None O
bees None O
di None O
sukkandiku None O
ngir None O
xam None O
ñaata None O
yoon None O
la None O
genn None O
feeñte None O
guy None O
tóllantiku None O
di None O
amal None O
ag None O
tóttantikoom None O
ci None O
benn None O
diiru None O
jamono None O
bees None O
jël None O
. None O

Breesil Breesil Breesil GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Hebe None O
Camargo None O
'' None O
' None O
( None O
8 None O
Maars None O
1929 None O
, None O
Taubaté None O
) None O
: None O
Breesilian Breesil Breesilian GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

Jëmm Jëmm Jëmm GPE 0.982273304022 Physics B-LOC

'' None O
'Osasco None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
dëkku None O
Breesil Breesil Breesil GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

Wersun Wersun Wersun GPE 0.679699169051 Black_seabream B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Monzón None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Ispaañ Ispaañ Ispaañ GPE 0.999996832097 Spain B-LOC
. None O

Laax None O
aw None O
ñam None O
la None O
wees None O
di None O
togge None O
ndox None O
, None O
sunguf None O
su None O
dugubi None O
suuna None O
ci None O
li None O
gën None O
a None O
bari None O
, None O
moo None O
xam None O
sees None O
araw None O
la None O
mbaa None O
muy None O
sanqal None O
, None O
moom None O
nag None O
ci None O
toggi None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
la None O
bokk None O
, None O
lekk None O
gu None O
yolom None O
lay None O
doon None O
te None O
ndoxe None O
, None O
deesi None O
jaxase None O
kook None O
soow None O
ci None O
li None O
ëpp None O
. None O

Santiago None O
de None O
los None O
Caballeros None O
de None O
Mérida None O
) None O
béne None O
deukkou None O
Benesuwela Benesuwela Benesuwela GPE 0.999991369034 Venezuela B-LOC
. None O

Santiago None O
Tequixquiax None O
) None O
béne None O
deukkou None O
Meksik Meksik Meksik GPE 0.999991744152 Mexico B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
Truong None O
Tan None O
Sang None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
njiitull None O
Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC
yi None O
( None O
2011-2016 None O
) None O
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Jeexiituwaay Jeexiituwaay_bu_Orsay Jeexiituwaay_bu_Orsay ORG 0.914639293236 Musée_d'Orsay B-ORG
bu None I-ORG
Orsay None I-ORG

Diggu Diggu_Aamerig Diggu_Aamerig GPE 0.679699169051 Central_America B-LOC
Aamerig None I-LOC

Feeñte None O
gi None O
li None O
muy None O
jur None O
mooy None O
ñakkug None O
kàttan Kàttanug_mbëj kàttan ORG 0.734924935788 Electrical_energy B-ORG
ci None O
biir None O
wommatukaay None O
, None O
di None O
soppaliku None O
tangoor None O
. None O

Beer Beer Beer GPE 0.995231144868 Gorée B-LOC

Tundi Tundi_Senegaal Tundi_Senegaal GPE 0.733996404965 Departments_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Diiwaanu Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru Diiwaanu_Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar_Region B-LOC
Ndakaaru None I-LOC

Ndakaaru Ndakaaru Ndakaaru GPE 1.0 Dakar B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Rafael None O
Correa None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
njiitull None O
Ekwadoor Ekwadoor Ekwadoor GPE 0.999990250159 Ecuador B-LOC
yi None O
( None O
2007-2013 None O
) None O
. None O

Réewum Réewum_Diggu_Afrig Réewum_Diggu_Afrig GPE 0.999996846848 Central_African_Republic B-LOC
Diggu None I-LOC
Afrig None I-LOC

Angolaa Angolaa Angolaa GPE 0.999996255094 Angola B-LOC

Tequixquiac None O
) None O
béne None O
municipality None O
Meksik Meksik Meksik GPE 0.999991744152 Mexico B-LOC
. None O

Pachuca None O
de None O
Soto None O
) None O
béne None O
city None O
Meksik Meksik Meksik GPE 0.999991744152 Mexico B-LOC
. None O

redirection None O
Tugal Tugal Tugal GPE 1.0 Europe B-LOC

Afritugalasi Afritugalasi Afritugalasi GPE 0.99999644039 Afro-Eurasia B-LOC

Duni Duni_Solomon Duni_Solomon GPE 1.0 Solomon_Islands B-LOC
Solomon None I-LOC

Endoneesi Endoneesi Endoneesi GPE 0.999992948029 Indonesia B-LOC

Seland-Gu-Bees Seland-Gu-Bees Seland-Gu-Bees GPE 0.99999999655 New_Zealand B-LOC

Dunu Dunu_Kook Dunu_Kook GPE 0.999998485832 Cook_Islands B-LOC
Kook None I-LOC

Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo GPE 0.999997203683 United_Kingdom B-LOC

Wanuatu Wanuatu Wanuatu GPE 0.999998899728 Vanuatu B-LOC

Diiwaan Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo GPE 0.99999348198 United_States B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC

Kaledooni-Gu-Bees Kaledooni-Gu-Bees Kaledooni-Gu-Bees GPE 0.979923066987 New_Caledonia B-LOC

Papuwaasi-Gine-Gu-Bees Papuwaasi-Gine-Gu-Bees Papuwaasi-Gine-Gu-Bees GPE 0.999993796375 Papua_New_Guinea B-LOC

Libi Libi Libi GPE 0.999999999984 Libya B-LOC

Mikroneesi Mikroneesi Mikroneesi GPE 0.980767615154 Micronesia B-LOC

Niwe Niwe Niwe GPE 0.999944457136 Niue B-LOC

Samowaa Samowaa Samowaa GPE 0.999999999996 Samoa B-LOC

Pitkeern Pitkeern Pitkeern GPE 0.99998773038 Pitcairn_Islands B-LOC

Kaledooni-Gu-Bees Kaledooni-Gu-Bees Kaledooni-Gu-Bees GPE 0.979923066987 New_Caledonia B-LOC

Polineesi Polineesi_gu_Faraas Polineesi_gu_Faraas GPE 0.981463541268 French_Polynesia B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Faraas None I-LOC

Wallis Wallis_ak_Futuna Wallis_ak_Futuna GPE 0.922399934174 Wallis_and_Futuna B-LOC
ak None I-LOC
Futuna None I-LOC

Arsantin Arsantin Arsantin GPE 0.999992179714 Argentina B-LOC

Breesil Breesil Breesil GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

Guyaana Guyaana_gu_Faraas Guyaana_gu_Faraas GPE 1.0 French_Guiana B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Faraas None I-LOC

Dunu Dunu_Falkland Dunu_Falkland GPE 0.999997193008 Falkland_Islands B-LOC
Falkland None I-LOC

Kamerun Kamerun Kamerun GPE 0.99999847838 Cameroon B-LOC

Kongóo-Kinshasa Kongóo-Kinshasa Kongóo-Kinshasa GPE 0.999997062197 Democratic_Republic_of_the_Congo B-LOC

Kongóo-Brasaawiil Kongóo-Brasaawiil Kongóo-Brasaawiil GPE 0.999996304931 Republic_of_the_Congo B-LOC

Bene Bene Bene GPE 0.999997650814 Benin B-LOC

redirection None O
Kodiwaar Kodiwaar Kodiwaar GPE 0.978326487531 Ivory_Coast B-LOC

Kasakistaan Kasakistaan Kasakistaan GPE 0.999996070922 Kazakhstan B-LOC

Tajikistaan Tajikistaan Tajikistaan GPE 0.999995608863 Tajikistan B-LOC

Mongoli Mongoli Mongoli GPE 0.999989145058 Mongolia B-LOC

Kore Kore_gu_Bëj-saalum Kore_gu_Bëj-saalum GPE 0.999999999954 South_Korea B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Bëj-saalum None I-LOC

Kore Kore_gu_Bëj-gànnaar Kore_gu_Bëj-gànnaar GPE 0.999999999929 North_Korea B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Bëj-gànnaar None I-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Réewum Réewum_Popileer_bu_Siin Réewum_Popileer_bu_Siin GPE 0.999999167165 China B-LOC
Popileer None I-LOC
bu None I-LOC
Siin None I-LOC

Kamboodi Kamboodi Kamboodi GPE 0.999992714953 Cambodia B-LOC

Timoor Timoor_gu_Penku Timoor_gu_Penku GPE 0.999999999959 East_Timor B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Penku None I-LOC

Diiwaani Diiwaani_Senegaal Diiwaani_Senegaal GPE 0.999977872861 Regions_of_Senegal B-LOC
Senegaal None I-LOC

Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC

Lu None O
bari None O
dañ None O
koy None O
xaaj None O
ñetti None O
gox None O
: None O
Afrig Afrig Afrig GPE 1.0 Africa B-LOC
, None O
Aamerig Aamerig Aamerig GPE 0.999999999956 Americas B-LOC
, None O
Asi Asi Asi GPE 0.999999991553 Asia B-LOC

Sapoŋ Sapoŋ Sapoŋ GPE 0.999984323433 Japan B-LOC

Siri Siri_Laanka Siri_Laanka GPE 0.99999999845 Sri_Lanka B-LOC
Laanka None I-LOC

Penku Penku_gu_Sori Penku_gu_Sori GPE 0.99999570246 Far_East B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Sori None I-LOC

Iraan Iraan Iraan GPE 0.999989905078 Iran B-LOC

Palestiin Palestiin Palestiin ORG 0.734924935788 Palestine_(region) B-ORG

Kowet Kowet Kowet GPE 0.999994887257 Kuwait B-LOC

Bahrayni Bahrayni Bahrayni GPE 0.999996971777 Bahrain B-LOC

Libaa Libaa Libaa GPE 0.999994874838 Lebanon B-LOC

Kataar Kataar Kataar GPE 0.999999999865 Qatar B-LOC

Siri Siri Siri GPE 0.999994189148 Syria B-LOC

Noorwees Noorwees Noorwees GPE 0.999854200889 Norway B-LOC

Riisi Riisi Riisi GPE 0.999995518192 Russia B-LOC

Moldaawi Moldaawi Moldaawi GPE 0.999994727044 Moldova B-LOC

Réewum Réewum_Maseduwaan Réewum_Maseduwaan GPE 0.999993345629 Republic_of_Macedonia B-LOC
Maseduwaan None I-LOC

Seerbi Seerbi Seerbi GPE 0.999992226335 Serbia B-LOC

Kore Kore_gu_Bëj-gànnaar Kore_gu_Bëj-gànnaar GPE 0.999999999929 North_Korea B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Bëj-gànnaar None I-LOC

Kore Kore_gu_Bëj-saalum Kore_gu_Bëj-saalum GPE 0.999999999954 South_Korea B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Bëj-saalum None I-LOC

Sapoŋ Sapoŋ Sapoŋ GPE 0.999984323433 Japan B-LOC

Mooy None O
làccu None O
bëj-gànnaar None O
wu None O
goxu Aamerig goxu_Aamerig GPE 0.999999999956 Americas B-LOC
Aamerig None I-LOC
. None O

Kanadaa Kanadaa Kanadaa GPE 0.999996263783 Canada B-LOC

Meksik Meksik Meksik GPE 0.999991744152 Mexico B-LOC

Afrig Afrig_gu_Bëj-saalum Afrig_gu_Bëj-saalum GPE 0.999997104528 South_Africa B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Bëj-saalum None I-LOC

Cadd Cadd Cadd GPE 0.922399934174 Chad B-LOC

Isipt Isipt Isipt GPE 0.999998703509 Egypt B-LOC

Gineg Gineg_yamoo Gineg_yamoo GPE 0.999995565381 Equatorial_Guinea B-LOC
yamoo None I-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Ron-goxu None O
End None O
'' None O
' None O
mi None O
ngi None O
nekk None O
ci None O
bëj-saalumu None O
Asi Asi Asi GPE 0.999999991553 Asia B-LOC
. None O

Banglaades Banglaades Banglaades GPE 0.999999999984 Bangladesh B-LOC

Butaan Butaan Butaan GPE 0.999985907067 Bhutan B-LOC

End End End GPE 0.999991154923 India B-LOC

Maldiif Maldiif Maldiif GPE 0.999999999564 Maldives B-LOC

Nepaal Nepaal Nepaal GPE 0.999992445487 Nepal B-LOC

Pakistaan Pakistaan Pakistaan GPE 0.999996416405 Pakistan B-LOC

Siri Siri_Laanka Siri_Laanka GPE 0.99999999845 Sri_Lanka B-LOC
Laanka None I-LOC

Rëy None O
gi None O
mu None O
rëy None O
ak None O
ni None O
mu None O
beroo None O
moo None O
tax None O
ñu None O
def None O
ko None O
ron-gon None O
, None O
li None O
fa None O
réewu None O
End End End GPE 0.999991154923 India B-LOC
gën None O
a None O
yaa None O
mo None O
tax None O
ñu None O
gox None O
ko None O
turam None O
. None O

Beliis Beliis Beliis GPE 0.99998796302 Belize B-LOC

Kosta Kosta_Riika Kosta_Riika GPE 0.999983130345 Costa_Rica B-LOC
Riika None I-LOC

Salbadoor Salbadoor Salbadoor GPE 0.999987811298 El_Salvador B-LOC

Panamaa Panamaa Panamaa GPE 0.999990205839 Panama B-LOC

Nikaraaguwa Nikaraaguwa Nikaraaguwa GPE 0.999983130345 Nicaragua B-LOC

Moo None O
taqaloo None O
ak None O
réew None O
yi None O
nekk None O
ci None O
Penku Penku_gu_Diggu Penku_gu_Diggu GPE 0.999417367962 Middle_East B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Diggu None I-LOC
gi None O
, None O
féete None O
ko None O
penku None O
, None O
di None O
: None O
Iraan None O
, None O
Afganistaan None O
, None O
Pakistaan None O
( None O
Di None O
yemoo None O
ak None O
baatu None O
waa None O
faraas None O
bi None O
di None O
''Moyen None O
Orient None O
'' None O
ak None O
bu None O
waa None O
angalteer None O
bi None O
di None O
`` None O
Middle None O
East None O
'' None O
) None O
. None O

Isipt Isipt Isipt GPE 0.999998703509 Egypt B-LOC

Israayil Israayil Israayil GPE 0.999992516157 Israel B-LOC

Palestiin Palestiin Palestiin ORG 0.734924935788 Palestine_(region) B-ORG

Jordaani Jordaani Jordaani GPE 0.999994503829 Jordan B-LOC

Iraak Iraak Iraak GPE 0.999990857863 Iraq B-LOC

Niseer Niseer Niseer GPE 0.999997227993 Niger B-LOC

Belaarus Belaarus Belaarus GPE 0.999995602846 Belarus B-LOC

Estooni Estooni Estooni GPE 0.999997941033 Estonia B-LOC

Letóoni Letóoni Letóoni GPE 0.999998814392 Latvia B-LOC

Lituwaani Lituwaani Lituwaani GPE 0.999996763656 Lithuania B-LOC

Riisi Riisi Riisi GPE 0.999995518192 Russia B-LOC

Romaani Romaani Romaani GPE 0.999990867634 Romania B-LOC

Moldaawi Moldaawi Moldaawi GPE 0.999994727044 Moldova B-LOC

Imbraatóor Imbraatóor_gu_Mali Imbraatóor_gu_Mali ORG 0.971760477912 Mali_Empire B-ORG
gu None I-ORG
Mali None I-ORG

Gànnaar Gànnaar Gànnaar GPE 0.999998358563 Mauritania B-LOC

Imbraatóor Imbraatóor_gu_Mali Imbraatóor_gu_Mali ORG 0.971760477912 Mali_Empire B-ORG
gu None I-ORG
Mali None I-ORG

Alseeri Alseeri Alseeri GPE 0.999995740238 Algeria B-LOC

Imbraatóor Imbraatóor_gu_Mali Imbraatóor_gu_Mali ORG 0.971760477912 Mali_Empire B-ORG
gu None I-ORG
Mali None I-ORG

Sudaan Sudaan Sudaan GPE 0.99999945476 Sudan B-LOC

Sahara Sahara_gu_Sowwu Sahara_gu_Sowwu GPE 0.999650615417 Western_Sahara B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Sowwu None I-LOC

Afrig Afrig_gu_Bëj-saalum Afrig_gu_Bëj-saalum GPE 0.999997104528 South_Africa B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Bëj-saalum None I-LOC

Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
ak None O
Mali Mali Mali GPE 0.999997745646 Mali B-LOC
lañu None O
gëna None O
nekk None O
. None O

Óstraali Óstraali Óstraali GPE 0.999999999348 Australia B-LOC

Melaneesi Melaneesi Melaneesi GPE 0.999850865084 Melanesia B-LOC

Mikroneesi Mikroneesi Mikroneesi GPE 0.980767615154 Micronesia B-LOC

Polineesi Polineesi Polineesi GPE 0.999850865084 Polynesia B-LOC

Seland-Gu-Bees Seland-Gu-Bees Seland-Gu-Bees GPE 0.99999999655 New_Zealand B-LOC

Madagaskaar Madagaskaar Madagaskaar GPE 0.999999999955 Madagascar B-LOC

Seysel Seysel Seysel GPE 0.999999999766 Seychelles B-LOC

Iraan Iraan Iraan GPE 0.999989905078 Iran B-LOC

Tirki Tirki Tirki GPE 0.922399934174 Turkey B-LOC

Iraak Iraak Iraak GPE 0.999990857863 Iraq B-LOC

Siri Siri Siri GPE 0.999994189148 Syria B-LOC

Israayil Israayil Israayil GPE 0.999992516157 Israel B-LOC

Palestiin Palestiin Palestiin ORG 0.734924935788 Palestine_(region) B-ORG

Araabi Araabi_Sawdit Araabi_Sawdit GPE 0.999991378209 Saudi_Arabia B-LOC
Sawdit None I-LOC

Kowet Kowet Kowet GPE 0.999994887257 Kuwait B-LOC

Imaaraat Imaaraat_yu_Araab_yu_Bennoo_yi Imaaraat_yu_Araab_yu_Bennoo_yi GPE 0.999995713824 United_Arab_Emirates B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Araab None I-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC
yi None I-LOC

Omaan Omaan Omaan GPE 0.999994341828 Oman B-LOC

Yaman Yaman Yaman GPE 0.999992919522 Yemen B-LOC

Kataar Kataar Kataar GPE 0.999999999865 Qatar B-LOC

Jordaani Jordaani Jordaani GPE 0.999994503829 Jordan B-LOC

Isipt Isipt Isipt GPE 0.999998703509 Egypt B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Bëj-saalum-penku None O
Asi None O
'' None O
' None O
ci None O
goxu Asi goxu_Asi GPE 0.999999991553 Asia B-LOC
Asi None I-LOC
la None O
bokk None O
. None O

Endoneesi Endoneesi Endoneesi GPE 0.999992948029 Indonesia B-LOC

Maleesi Maleesi Maleesi GPE 0.999998082645 Malaysia B-LOC

Miyanmaar Miyanmaar Miyanmaar ORG 0.734924935788 Myanmar B-ORG

Filipiin Filipiin Filipiin GPE 0.999999999318 Philippines B-LOC

Singapoor Singapoor Singapoor GPE 0.999999866437 Singapore B-LOC

Taaylaand Taaylaand Taaylaand GPE 0.999988046216 Thailand B-LOC

Timoor Timoor_gu_Penku Timoor_gu_Penku GPE 0.999999999959 East_Timor B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Penku None I-LOC

Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam Wiyetnaam GPE 0.999988951935 Vietnam B-LOC

Ugandaa Ugandaa Ugandaa GPE 0.999935749545 Uganda B-LOC

Ruwandaa Ruwandaa Ruwandaa GPE 0.999998328267 Rwanda B-LOC

Keeñaa Keeñaa Keeñaa GPE 0.999996929882 Kenya B-LOC

Eritere Eritere Eritere GPE 0.999992862604 Eritrea B-LOC

Somali Somali Somali GPE 0.999999999986 Somalia B-LOC

Eritere Eritere Eritere GPE 0.999992862604 Eritrea B-LOC

Tansani Tansani Tansani GPE 0.999997571979 Tanzania B-LOC

Jibuti Jibuti Jibuti GPE 0.999997722281 Djibouti B-LOC

Simbaawee Simbaawee Simbaawee GPE 0.999829908008 Zimbabwe B-LOC

Mosambik Mosambik Mosambik GPE 0.999997247099 Mozambique B-LOC

End End End GPE 0.999991154923 India B-LOC

Diiwaan Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo Diiwaan_yu_Bennoo GPE 0.99999348198 United_States B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC

Bejjenu Bejjenu_Afrig Bejjenu_Afrig GPE 0.999999999991 Horn_of_Africa B-LOC
Afrig None I-LOC

Sowwu Sowwu_Afrig Sowwu_Afrig GPE 0.679699169051 West_Africa B-LOC
Afrig None I-LOC

Marok Marok Marok GPE 0.999997611307 Morocco B-LOC

Ci None O
lu None O
ëpp None O
da None O
ñuy None O
wax None O
naa None O
Ispaañ Ispaañ Ispaañ GPE 0.999996832097 Spain B-LOC
, None O
Itaali Itaali Itaali GPE 0.999994576668 Italy B-LOC
, None O
Girees Girees Girees GPE 0.999468851293 Greece B-LOC
, None O
ñooy None O
réew None O
yi None O
ci None O
bokk None O
, None O
daanaka None O
ci None O
lu None O
daj None O
réew None O
yépp None O
yi None O
nekk None O
ci None O
Géej Géej_gu_Diggu Géej_gu_Diggu GPE 0.999999127545 Mediterranean_Sea B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Diggu None I-LOC
gi None O
. None O

Portugaal Portugaal Portugaal GPE 0.999995605305 Portugal B-LOC

Ispaañ Ispaañ Ispaañ GPE 0.999996832097 Spain B-LOC

Andoor Andoor Andoor GPE 0.999989201816 Andorra B-LOC

Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC

Itaali Itaali Itaali GPE 0.999994576668 Italy B-LOC

Korwaasi Korwaasi Korwaasi GPE 0.999996710561 Croatia B-LOC

Girees Girees Girees GPE 0.999468851293 Greece B-LOC

Albaani Albaani Albaani GPE 0.999996663787 Albania B-LOC

Montenegro Montenegro Montenegro GPE 0.999656339701 Montenegro B-LOC

Réewum Réewum_Maseduwaan Réewum_Maseduwaan GPE 0.999993345629 Republic_of_Macedonia B-LOC
Maseduwaan None I-LOC

Seerbi Seerbi Seerbi GPE 0.999992226335 Serbia B-LOC

Esloweeni Esloweeni Esloweeni GPE 0.999995415738 Slovenia B-LOC

Ciipër Ciipër Ciipër GPE 1.0 Cyprus B-LOC

Malt Malt Malt GPE 1.0 Malta B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Bëj-gànnaaru None O
Tugal None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
wàll None O
gu None O
Bëj-gànnaar None O
gu None O
goxu Tugal goxu_Tugal GPE 1.0 Europe B-LOC
Tugal None I-LOC
. None O

Danmaark Danmaark Danmaark GPE 0.999999999818 Denmark B-LOC

Islaand Islaand Islaand GPE 0.999999999671 Iceland B-LOC

Finlaand Finlaand Finlaand GPE 0.999994932457 Finland B-LOC

Estooni Estooni Estooni GPE 0.999997941033 Estonia B-LOC

Letóoni Letóoni Letóoni GPE 0.999998814392 Latvia B-LOC

Lituwaani Lituwaani Lituwaani GPE 0.999996763656 Lithuania B-LOC

Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo GPE 0.999997203683 United_Kingdom B-LOC

Almaañ Almaañ Almaañ GPE 0.999994565441 Germany B-LOC

Poloñ Poloñ Poloñ GPE 0.999995090538 Poland B-LOC

Danmaark Danmaark Danmaark GPE 0.999999999818 Denmark B-LOC

Islaand Islaand Islaand GPE 0.999999999671 Iceland B-LOC

Finlaand Finlaand Finlaand GPE 0.999994932457 Finland B-LOC

Estooni Estooni Estooni GPE 0.999997941033 Estonia B-LOC

Letóoni Letóoni Letóoni GPE 0.999998814392 Latvia B-LOC

Lituwaani Lituwaani Lituwaani GPE 0.999996763656 Lithuania B-LOC

Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo GPE 0.999997203683 United_Kingdom B-LOC

Jibuti Jibuti Jibuti GPE 0.999997722281 Djibouti B-LOC

Eritere Eritere Eritere GPE 0.999992862604 Eritrea B-LOC

Ecoopi Ecoopi Ecoopi GPE 0.999992867998 Ethiopia B-LOC

Somali Somali Somali GPE 0.999999999986 Somalia B-LOC

Li None O
ko None O
lëkkaleek None O
Bëj-gànnaaru None O
Aamerik None O
mooy None O
Panamaa Panamaa Panamaa GPE 0.999990205839 Panama B-LOC
. None O

Ay None O
askan None O
yu None O
jòge None O
woon None O
goxub None O
Asi Asi Asi GPE 0.999999991553 Asia B-LOC
ñoo None O
ko None O
dëkkee None O
woon None O
, None O
daanaka None O
am None O
na None O
ay None O
junniy None O
at None O
nj.j None O
. None O

Arsantin Arsantin Arsantin GPE 0.999992179714 Argentina B-LOC

Boliibi Boliibi Boliibi GPE 0.999990879761 Bolivia B-LOC

Koloombi Koloombi Koloombi GPE 0.999990322221 Colombia B-LOC

Ekwadoor Ekwadoor Ekwadoor GPE 0.999990250159 Ecuador B-LOC

Guyaana Guyaana Guyaana GPE 0.999996436556 Guyana B-LOC

Panamaa Panamaa Panamaa GPE 0.999990205839 Panama B-LOC

Paraguwaay Paraguwaay Paraguwaay GPE 0.999991024394 Paraguay B-LOC

Peru Peru Peru GPE 0.999990091791 Peru B-LOC

Uruguwaay Uruguwaay Uruguwaay GPE 0.999990722889 Uruguay B-LOC

Benesuwela Benesuwela Benesuwela GPE 0.999991369034 Venezuela B-LOC

Guyaana Guyaana_gu_Faraas Guyaana_gu_Faraas GPE 1.0 French_Guiana B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Faraas None I-LOC
( None O
Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC
) None O

Dunu Dunu_Falkland Dunu_Falkland GPE 0.999997193008 Falkland_Islands B-LOC
Falkland None I-LOC
( None O
Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo Nguur-Yu-Bennoo GPE 0.999997203683 United_Kingdom B-LOC
) None O

Cadd Cadd Cadd GPE 0.922399934174 Chad B-LOC

Gaboŋ Gaboŋ Gaboŋ GPE 0.999997358201 Gabon B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Lebu None O
'' None O
' None O
, None O
mooy None O
benn None O
waaso None O
nekk None O
ci None O
reewum None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
. None O

Seex Seex_Anta_Jóob Seex_Anta_Jóob PER 0.999999275085 Cheikh_Anta_Diop B-PER
Anta None I-PER
Jóob None I-PER
, None O
ci None O
gestoom None O
, None O
da None O
wone None O
ni None O
, None O
li None O
ñu None O
tudde None O
lebu None O
, None O
am None O
na None O
lu None O
mu None O
bokk None O
ak None O
tur None O
boobu None O
ñu None O
joxe None O
reewum None O
Libi Libi Libi GPE 0.999999999984 Libya B-LOC
. None O

Dañoo None O
mujj None O
daw None O
dëkk None O
boobu None O
, None O
ndax None O
amoon None O
na None O
benn None O
askan None O
bu None O
ñowoon None O
foofu None O
, None O
joge None O
Asi Asi Asi GPE 0.999999991553 Asia B-LOC
, None O
te None O
ñu None O
leen None O
daan None O
begga None O
noot None O
. None O

Sudaan Sudaan Sudaan GPE 0.99999945476 Sudan B-LOC
, None O
mooy None O
dëkk None O
bi None O
Lebu None O
yi None O
baawo None O
, None O
ñu None O
ko None O
gëna None O
raññe None O
ci None O
turu None O
Nubi None O
walla None O
Kuus None O
. None O

Ñu None O
bare None O
bokk None O
ci None O
Tariqa None O
Tijaan None O
, None O
ak None O
Layeen None O
yi None O
( None O
Seydinaa Seydinaa_Limaamu_Laay Seydinaa_Limaamu_Laay PER 0.999662428343 Seydina_Mouhammadou_Limamou_Laye B-PER
Limaamu None I-PER
Laay None I-PER
) None O
. None O

Ci None O
araab None O
' None O
'' None O
Maghreb None O
'' None O
' None O
day None O
tekki None O
tamit None O
Marok Marok Marok GPE 0.999997611307 Morocco B-LOC
. None O

Alaaji Alaaji_Omar_Fuutiyu_TAAL Alaaji_Omar_Fuutiyu_TAAL PER 0.924286536099 El_Hadj_Umar_Tall B-PER
Omar None I-PER
Fuutiyu None I-PER
TAAL None I-PER

Botswana Botswana Botswana GPE 0.999997230392 Botswana B-LOC

Lesoto Lesoto Lesoto GPE 0.999997810723 Lesotho B-LOC

Namibi Namibi Namibi GPE 0.999997285429 Namibia B-LOC

Suwaasilaand Suwaasilaand Suwaasilaand GPE 0.999997281418 Swaziland B-LOC

Malawi Malawi Malawi GPE 0.999997827871 Malawi B-LOC

Madagaskaar Madagaskaar Madagaskaar GPE 0.999999999955 Madagascar B-LOC

Mosambik Mosambik Mosambik GPE 0.999997247099 Mozambique B-LOC

Saambi Saambi Saambi GPE 0.999997827871 Zambia B-LOC

Móoris Móoris Móoris GPE 0.999999999163 Mauritius B-LOC

Komoor Komoor Komoor GPE 0.999997734513 Comoros B-LOC

Simbaawee Simbaawee Simbaawee GPE 0.999829908008 Zimbabwe B-LOC

Isipt Isipt Isipt GPE 0.999998703509 Egypt B-LOC

Sahara Sahara_gu_Sowwu Sahara_gu_Sowwu GPE 0.999650615417 Western_Sahara B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Sowwu None I-LOC

Àdduna Àdduna Àdduna ORG 0.9254528284 World B-ORG

Mbàmbulaanug Mbàmbulaanug_End Mbàmbulaanug_End GPE 0.605228959361 Indian_Ocean B-LOC
End None I-LOC

Onduras Onduras Onduras GPE 0.999989804326 Honduras B-LOC

Onduras Onduras Onduras GPE 0.999989804326 Honduras B-LOC

Alseeri Alseeri Alseeri GPE 0.999995740238 Algeria B-LOC

Isipt Isipt Isipt GPE 0.999998703509 Egypt B-LOC

Libi Libi Libi GPE 0.999999999984 Libya B-LOC

Marok Marok Marok GPE 0.999997611307 Morocco B-LOC

Sudaan Sudaan Sudaan GPE 0.99999945476 Sudan B-LOC

Tiniisi Tiniisi Tiniisi GPE 0.999998141186 Tunisia B-LOC

Sahara Sahara_gu_Sowwu Sahara_gu_Sowwu GPE 0.999650615417 Western_Sahara B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Sowwu None I-LOC

Maghreb Maghreb Maghreb GPE 0.999999999998 Maghreb B-LOC
( None O
sowu None O
ci None O
araab None O
) None O
, None O
moo None O
ëmb None O
réew None O
yii None O
: None O
Gànnaar Gànnaar Gànnaar GPE 0.999998358563 Mauritania B-LOC
, None O
Marok Marok Marok GPE 0.999997611307 Morocco B-LOC
, None O
Alseeri Alseeri Alseeri GPE 0.999995740238 Algeria B-LOC
, None O
Tiniisi Tiniisi Tiniisi GPE 0.999998141186 Tunisia B-LOC
ak None O
Libi Libi Libi GPE 0.999999999984 Libya B-LOC
. None O

Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
; None O

Gànnaar Gànnaar Gànnaar GPE 0.999998358563 Mauritania B-LOC
; None O

Mali Mali Mali GPE 0.999997745646 Mali B-LOC
; None O

Niseer Niseer Niseer GPE 0.999997227993 Niger B-LOC
; None O

Niseeria Niseeria Niseeria GPE 0.999998094206 Nigeria B-LOC
; None O

Cadd Cadd Cadd GPE 0.922399934174 Chad B-LOC
; None O

Sudaan Sudaan Sudaan GPE 0.99999945476 Sudan B-LOC
. None O

Seex Seex_Anta_Jóob Seex_Anta_Jóob PER 0.999999275085 Cheikh_Anta_Diop B-PER
Anta None I-PER
Jóob None I-PER
( None O
1923 None O
– None O
1986 None O
g.j None O
) None O
moom None O
lañuy None O
jàppe None O
boroom None O
xam-xam None O
bu None O
Senegaal None O
bi None O
jot None O
a None O
def None O
ay None O
gëstu None O
ci None O
nguurug None O
Isipt None O
gu None O
yàgg None O
ga None O
, None O
mu None O
leeral None O
ci None O
séqoo None O
gi None O
am None O
ci None O
diggante None O
xayug None O
Isipt None O
ak None O
xayug None O
waa None O
Afrig None O
yu None O
ñuul None O
yi None O
. None O

Kongóo-Brasaawiil Kongóo-Brasaawiil Kongóo-Brasaawiil GPE 0.999996304931 Republic_of_the_Congo B-LOC

Ñenn None O
ñi None O
di None O
boole None O
Afrig Afrig Afrig GPE 1.0 Africa B-LOC
Tugal Tugal Tugal GPE 1.0 Europe B-LOC
ak None O
Asi Asi Asi GPE 0.999999991553 Asia B-LOC
mu None O
doon None O
Afritugalasi Afritugalasi Afritugalasi GPE 0.99999644039 Afro-Eurasia B-LOC
. None O

' None O
'' None O
6 None O
gox None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
Afrig None O
, None O
Bëj-gànnaaru None O
Aamerig None O
, None O
bëj-saalumu None O
Aamerig None O
, None O
Tugalasi Tugalasi Tugalasi GPE 0.999999999877 Eurasia B-LOC
, None O
Oseyaani None O
, None O
Dottu None O
Bëj-saalum None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
5 None O
gox None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
Afrig None O
, None O
Aamerig Aamerig Aamerig GPE 0.999999999956 Americas B-LOC
, None O
Tugal None O
, None O
Oseyaani None O
, None O
Asi None O
. None O

' None O
'' None O
4 None O
gox None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
Aamerig None O
, None O
Afritugalasi Afritugalasi Afritugalasi GPE 0.99999644039 Afro-Eurasia B-LOC
, None O
Oseyaani None O
, None O
Dottu None O
Bëj-saalum None O
. None O

Kongóo-Kinshasa Kongóo-Kinshasa Kongóo-Kinshasa GPE 0.999997062197 Democratic_Republic_of_the_Congo B-LOC

redirection None O
Libarwil Libarwil Libarwil GPE 1.0 Libreville B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Penku None O
Afrig None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
wàllu None O
Afrig Afrig Afrig GPE 1.0 Africa B-LOC
gi None O
gën None O
a None O
féete None O
penku None O
. None O

Eritere Eritere Eritere GPE 0.999992862604 Eritrea B-LOC

Ecoopi Ecoopi Ecoopi GPE 0.999992867998 Ethiopia B-LOC

Jibuti Jibuti Jibuti GPE 0.999997722281 Djibouti B-LOC

Somali Somali Somali GPE 0.999999999986 Somalia B-LOC

Keeñaa Keeñaa Keeñaa GPE 0.999996929882 Kenya B-LOC

Ugandaa Ugandaa Ugandaa GPE 0.999935749545 Uganda B-LOC

Tansani Tansani Tansani GPE 0.999997571979 Tanzania B-LOC

Ruwandaa Ruwandaa Ruwandaa GPE 0.999998328267 Rwanda B-LOC

Buruundi Buruundi Buruundi GPE 0.999995626681 Burundi B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Libarwil None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
réewum None O
Gaboŋ Gaboŋ Gaboŋ GPE 0.999997358201 Gabon B-LOC
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Libarwil Libarwil Libarwil GPE 1.0 Libreville B-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Xayra Xayra Xayra GPE 1.0 Cairo B-LOC

REDIRECTION None O
Imaaraat Imaaraat_yu_Araab_yu_Bennoo_yi Imaaraat_yu_Araab_yu_Bennoo_yi GPE 0.999995713824 United_Arab_Emirates B-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Araab None I-LOC
yu None I-LOC
Bennoo None I-LOC
yi None I-LOC

Mi None O
ngi None O
féete None O
ci None O
bëj-gànnaar-sowwu None O
réew None O
mi None O
, None O
taq None O
ci None O
tàkk None O
gi None O
, None O
ci None O
dogub None O
suuf None O
bu None O
kekke None O
, None O
féetek None O
Géej Géej_gu_Diggu Géej_gu_Diggu GPE 0.999999127545 Mediterranean_Sea B-LOC
gu None I-LOC
Diggu None I-LOC
gi None O
ci None O
geneen None O
wàll None O

' None O
'' None O
Siin-Saalum None O
'' None O
' None O
bokk None O
nañ None O
ci None O
nguuri None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
yi None O
fi None O
nekkoon None O
. None O

Ci None O
noonu None O
ngir None O
bañ None O
a None O
tuub None O
, None O
ñu None O
taamu None O
gàddaay None O
, None O
wàcc None O
jëm None O
bëj-saalum None O
ca None O
Jolof Jolof Jolof GPE 0.795338880767 Jolof_Empire B-LOC
. None O

Jolof Jolof Jolof GPE 0.795338880767 Jolof_Empire B-LOC

Waalo Waalo Waalo GPE 0.778036037681 Waalo B-LOC

Kajoor Kajoor Kajoor ORG 0.971760477912 Cayor B-ORG

Bawol Bawol Bawol ORG 0.682608524192 Baol B-ORG

REDIRECTION None O
Seex Seex_Anta_Jóob Seex_Anta_Jóob PER 0.999999275085 Cheikh_Anta_Diop B-PER
Anta None I-PER
Jóob None I-PER

REDIRECTION None O
Pari Pari Pari GPE 1.0 Paris B-LOC

Planoise Planoise Planoise GPE 0.999999998572 Planoise B-LOC

Albert Albert_Einstein Albert_Einstein PER 0.999999995993 Albert_Einstein B-PER
Einstein None I-PER

Jëmm Jëmm Jëmm GPE 0.982273304022 Physics B-LOC

Mi None O
ngi None O
tambalee None O
ca None O
Niseeria Niseeria Niseeria GPE 0.999998094206 Nigeria B-LOC
ba None O
ci None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
. None O

Gana Gana Gana GPE 0.999993298362 Ghana B-LOC

Libeeria Libeeria Libeeria GPE 0.999994592957 Liberia B-LOC

Mali Mali Mali GPE 0.999997745646 Mali B-LOC

Gànnaar Gànnaar Gànnaar GPE 0.999998358563 Mauritania B-LOC

Niseer Niseer Niseer GPE 0.999997227993 Niger B-LOC

Niseeria Niseeria Niseeria GPE 0.999998094206 Nigeria B-LOC

Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC

Siraa Siraa_Leyoon Siraa_Leyoon GPE 0.999998178618 Sierra_Leone B-LOC
Leyoon None I-LOC

Togóo Togóo Togóo GPE 0.999997650814 Togo B-LOC

Gana Gana Gana GPE 0.999993298362 Ghana B-LOC

Libeeria Libeeria Libeeria GPE 0.999994592957 Liberia B-LOC

Gànnaar Gànnaar Gànnaar GPE 0.999998358563 Mauritania B-LOC

Niseer Niseer Niseer GPE 0.999997227993 Niger B-LOC

Niseeria Niseeria Niseeria GPE 0.999998094206 Nigeria B-LOC

Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC

Siraa Siraa_Leyoon Siraa_Leyoon GPE 0.999998178618 Sierra_Leone B-LOC
Leyoon None I-LOC

Togóo Togóo Togóo GPE 0.999997650814 Togo B-LOC

Cadd Cadd Cadd GPE 0.922399934174 Chad B-LOC

Mali Mali Mali GPE 0.999997745646 Mali B-LOC

Niseer Niseer Niseer GPE 0.999997227993 Niger B-LOC

Kàttanug Kàttanug_mbëj Kàttanug_mbëj ORG 0.734924935788 Electrical_energy B-ORG
mbëj None I-ORG

Gu None O
waa Faraas waa_faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC
faraas None I-LOC
teggu None O
ci None O
23 None O
gamu None O
2001 None O
, None O
gu None O
waa None O
almaañ None O
tegu None O
ci None O
ak None O
yeneen None O
yépp None O
, None O
ba None O
tay None O
ci None O
atum None O
2007 None O
mat None O
nañu None O
ñaari-téeméer None O
ak None O
juróom-fukki None O
làkk None O
. None O

Kàttanug Kàttanug_imbiku Kàttanug_imbiku PER 0.305349190835 Kinetic_energy B-PER
imbiku None I-PER
( None O
cinétique None O
) None O

Kàttanug Kàttanug_mbëj Kàttanug_mbëj ORG 0.734924935788 Electrical_energy B-ORG
mbëj None I-ORG

Lonkoyoon None O
wu None O
Abraham None O
Cresques None O
, None O
bi None O
ko None O
buuru None O
Faraas Faraas Faraas GPE 0.999997637559 France B-LOC
defloo None O
woon None O
Charles None O
V None O
, None O
bindoon None O
na None O
fa None O
turu None O
péeyam None O
`` None O
Ciuta None O
de None O
Malli None O
'' None O
. None O

Tekuruur None O
jàll None O
ci None O
loxoy None O
wolof None O
yi None O
( None O
Jolof Jolof Jolof GPE 0.795338880767 Jolof_Empire B-LOC
) None O
. None O

Ki None O
ñuy None O
wax None O
ne None O
moo None O
ko None O
wuññi None O
mooy None O
Ernest None O
Rutherford None O
, None O
donte None O
jëmmaan Jëmm jëmmaan GPE 0.982273304022 Physics B-LOC
bu None O
waa-almaañ Almaañ waa-almaañ GPE 0.999994565441 Germany B-LOC
bi None O
Eugene None O
Goldstein None O
njoortoon None O
na None O
ag None O
nekkam None O
njëkk None O
ngir None O
manoon None O
a None O
dëggal None O
ay None O
gëstoom None O
. None O

Ngir None O
woomle None O
gu None O
réy None O
gi None O
gox None O
bi None O
def None O
ci None O
wàllug None O
mbay None O
, None O
dundat None O
ak None O
mbell None O
, None O
sancaani None O
sowwu None O
yi None O
( None O
waa None O
Tugal None O
yi None O
) None O
tegoon None O
nañu None O
ko None O
loxo None O
, None O
waaye None O
ay None O
askanam None O
jug None O
def None O
ay None O
fipp None O
yu None O
toftaloo None O
ngir None O
gore None O
ci None O
canc None O
gi None O
( None O
colonialisme None O
) None O
, None O
ci None O
noonu None O
ñu None O
ёpp None O
ci None O
ñoom None O
mujj None O
temb None O
, None O
sancu None O
yi None O
ci None O
mujj None O
a None O
temb None O
nag None O
ñooy None O
yu None O
Portugaal Portugaal Portugaal GPE 0.999995605305 Portugal B-LOC
yi None O
, None O
ñoom None O
de None O
xeex None O
nañu None O
xeex None O
yu None O
tar None O
ngir None O
jot None O
séenug None O
tembte None O
. None O

Doji None O
géej None O
gu None O
xonq None O
gi None O
: None O
càllalag None O
doj None O
la None O
gu None O
kawe None O
, None O
tàlleeku None O
bawoo None O
bёj-gànnaar None O
, None O
ba None O
bёj-saalum None O
, None O
feggook None O
nag None O
tefes None O
gu None O
sowwu None O
gu None O
géej None O
gu None O
xonq None O
gi None O
ci None O
Isipt Isipt Isipt GPE 0.999998703509 Egypt B-LOC
ak None O
Sudaan Sudaan Sudaan GPE 0.99999945476 Sudan B-LOC
. None O

Tawi None O
Yamoo None O
yu None O
bari None O
yi None O
danañuy None O
faral None O
a None O
sottiku None O
ci None O
tefesug None O
Gana Gana Gana GPE 0.999993298362 Ghana B-LOC
gi None O
, None O
ak None O
[Mbalkam None O
Kongóo|mbalkam None O
Kongóo]] None O
mi None O
diirub None O
at None O
mépp None O
. None O

Kàttanug Kàttanug_mbëj Kàttanug_mbëj ORG 0.734924935788 Electrical_energy B-ORG
mbëj None I-ORG

Feppsaal Feppsaal Feppsaal ORG 0.551542179316 Proton B-ORG

Feppmaandu Feppmaandu Feppmaandu ORG 0.551542179316 Neutron B-ORG

'' None O
V None O
'' None O
dend Dendu_mbëj dend PER 0.305349190835 Voltage B-PER
bi None O
. None O

Kàttanug Kàttanug_mbëj Kàttanug_mbëj ORG 0.734924935788 Electrical_energy B-ORG
mbëj None I-ORG

Dëgërlukaay Dëgërlukaay Dëgërlukaay ORG 0.489799526672 Resistor B-ORG

REDIRECTION None O
Kumba Kumba_Ndóofeen_Famak_Juuf Kumba_Ndóofeen_Famak_Juuf PER 0.999914726257 Maad_a_Sinig_Kumba_Ndoffene_Famak_Joof B-PER
Ndóofeen None I-PER
Famak None I-PER
Juuf None I-PER

' None O
'' None O
Arara None O
'' None O
' None O
: None O
dëkku None O
Breesil Breesil Breesil GPE 0.999991615385 Brazil B-LOC

' None O
'' None O
Santiag None O
'' None O
' None O
mooy None O
péeyu None O
rééwum None O
Sili Sili Sili GPE 0.999989425747 Chile B-LOC
. None O

Dëgërlukaay Dëgërlukaay Dëgërlukaay ORG 0.489799526672 Resistor B-ORG

' None O
'' None O
Korent None O
'' None O
' None O
benn None O
diiwaan None O
ci None O
yu None O
Girees Girees Girees GPE 0.999468851293 Greece B-LOC
. None O

REDIRECTION None O
Kumba Kumba_Ndóofeen_Famak_Juuf Kumba_Ndóofeen_Famak_Juuf PER 0.999914726257 Maad_a_Sinig_Kumba_Ndoffene_Famak_Joof B-PER
Ndóofeen None I-PER
Famak None I-PER
Juuf None I-PER

' None O
'' None O
Łobez None O
'' None O
' None O
ab None O
dëkku-kaw None O
la None O
ca None O
bëj-saalum-penkug None O
Poloñ Poloñ Poloñ GPE 0.999995090538 Poland B-LOC
. None O

Image None O
: None O
Flag None O
of None O
Mali None O
1959-1961.svg|Raaya None O
Mbooloom None O
mu None O
Mali None O
ma None O
, None O
boolewoon None O
Senegaal Senegaal Senegaal GPE 0.999997650814 Senegal B-LOC
ak None O
Mali Mali Mali GPE 0.999997745646 Mali B-LOC
( None O
1959-1960 None O
) None O

