# sent_id = ap.42.monbeg-1
# doc_id = urn:cts:copticLit:ap.42.monbeg
# segmentation = gold
# tagging = checked
# parsing = automatic
# entities = gold
1	ⲁ	ⲁ	_	APST	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
2	ⲩ	ⲛⲧⲟⲟⲩ	_	PPERS	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
3	ϫⲟⲟ	ϫⲱ	_	V	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
4	ⲥ	ⲛⲧⲟⲥ	_	PPERO	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
5	ⲉⲧⲃⲉ	ⲉⲧⲃⲉ	_	PREP	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
6	ⲧ	ⲡ	_	ART	_	_	_	_	Entity=B-person
7	ⲙⲁⲕⲁⲣⲓⲁ	ⲙⲁⲕⲁⲣⲓⲁ	_	N	_	_	_	_	Entity=I-person
8	ⲥⲁⲣⲁ	ⲥⲁⲣⲁ	_	NPROP	_	_	_	_	Entity=I-person
9	ⲧ	ⲡ	_	ART	_	_	_	_	Entity=I-person
10	ⲡⲁⲣⲑⲉⲛⲟⲥ	ⲡⲁⲣⲑⲉⲛⲟⲥ	_	N	_	_	_	_	Entity=I-person
11	ϫⲉ	ϫⲉ	_	CONJ	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
12	ⲁ	ⲁ	_	APST	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
13	ⲥ	ⲛⲧⲟⲥ	_	PPERS	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
14	ⲉⲣ	ⲉⲓⲣⲉ	_	V	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
15	ⲥⲉ	ⲥⲉ	_	NUM	_	_	_	_	Entity=B-time
16	ⲛ	ⲛ	_	PREP	_	_	_	_	Entity=I-time
17	ⲣⲟⲙⲡⲉ	ⲣⲟⲙⲡⲉ	_	N	_	_	_	_	Entity=I-time
18	ⲉ	ⲉⲣⲉ	_	CCIRC	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
19	ⲥ	ⲛⲧⲟⲥ	_	PPERS	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
20	ⲟⲩⲏϩ	ⲟⲩⲱϩ	_	VSTAT	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
21	ⲙ	ⲛ	_	PREP	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
22	ⲡⲉ	ⲡ	_	ART	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
23	ⲧⲡⲉ	ⲧⲡⲉ	_	N	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
24	ⲙ	ⲛ	_	PREP	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
25	ⲡ	ⲡ	_	ART	_	_	_	_	Entity=B-place
26	ⲓⲉⲣⲟ	ⲓⲉⲣⲟ	_	N	_	_	_	_	Entity=I-place
27	.	.	_	PUNCT	_	_	_	_	Entity=O


# sent_id = ap.42.monbeg-2
# doc_id = urn:cts:copticLit:ap.42.monbeg
# segmentation = gold
# tagging = checked
# parsing = automatic
# entities = gold
1	ⲙⲡⲉ	ⲙⲡⲉ	_	ANEGPST	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
2	ⲥ	ⲛⲧⲟⲥ	_	PPERS	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
3	ⲕⲉ	ⲕⲉ	_	V	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
4	ⲣⲁⲧ	ⲣⲁⲧ	_	N	_	_	_	_	Entity=B-object
5	ⲥ	ⲛⲧⲟⲥ	_	PPERO	_	_	_	_	Entity=I-object
6	ⲉⲃⲟⲗ	ⲉⲃⲟⲗ	_	ADV	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
7	ⲉⲛⲉϩ	ⲉⲛⲉϩ	_	ADV	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
8	ⲉ	ⲉ	_	PREP	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
9	ⲛⲁⲩ	ⲛⲁⲩ	_	V	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
10	ⲉ	ⲉ	_	PREP	_	_	_	_	Entity=O
11	ⲡ	ⲡ	_	ART	_	_	_	_	Entity=B-place
12	ⲓⲉⲣⲟ	ⲓⲉⲣⲟ	_	N	_	_	_	_	Entity=I-place
13	.	.	_	PUNCT	_	_	_	_	Entity=O

